<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for WV</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for WV</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:43:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024090943</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024090943&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-09-18T09:15:04+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-13&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: NITRO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WV&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ABF FREIGHT SYSTEM, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Ellen Crislip, 252 Operations Supervisor, contacted Safety regarding a UN1760 spill to the dock floor. Ellen Crislip advised Safety that while Steve Looney, dock worker, was unloading the freight one box was punctured by the forklift. Ellen Crislip stated a piece of the wood on the pallet broke caus ing the box to fall below the pallet resulting in the box being punctured. Ellen Crislip advised they placed pads down to soak the spill and the box is now upright not leaking. Ellen Crislip stated the dock worker was attempting to clean the spill in house. Safety directed Ellen Crislip to stop the dock worker. Safety stated Cura would need to be contacted for remediation. Ellen Crislip advised Cura to be contacted on straight time since the spill is contained. ~&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024090943</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 09:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
