<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MI</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2023091052</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2196678&gt;X-2023091052&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2196678&gt;X-2023091052&lt;/A"&gt;Report X-2023091052&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-10-27T18:13:30+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-09-14&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: PORTAGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Package was coded as damaged by P&amp;amp;D driver and was found on van with granules spilling out of box. Package was removed from the vehicle, placed in a HazMat tote, and taken to HazMat cage using proper PPE, where it was discovered that bottom of drum became cracked, causing contents to spill out. DescribePack: Roughly 6&amp;quot; crack on bottom of jug, causing contents to spill out bottom DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Package was removed from the vehicle, placed in a HazMat tote, and taken to HazMat cage using proper PPE. Vehicle was swept out and extra granules consolidated with rest of package.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2023091052</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2023100573</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2198618&gt;E-2023100573&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2198618&gt;E-2023100573&lt;/A"&gt;Report E-2023100573&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-10-23T15:12:15+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-09-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DETROIT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CONSOLIDATED RAIL CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On September 24, 2023 at 20:37 Transportation personnel in the Conrail Livernois Terminal reported that ,GATX 2013  a loaded tank car of FLUOROSILICIC ACID leaking from top of the tank car upon movement. Additionally,  during routine switching operations a Conrail Conductor was splashed with acid from the improperly secured tank car. The Conductor was immediately brought in to remove affected clothing and shower of any impacted skin. No reportable injury was encountered as the Conductors and Terminal Supervisions actions removed all material before any health effects took place. The car was isolated and the shipper/consignee PVS was notified directly via phone. Enviroserve, an approved Conrail Contractor was notified to respond, inspect and secure the tank car. Enviroserve personnel, investigated the leak and found the source of the leak to be from the rupture disk assembly. Upon further inspection it was found that the inspection cap was hanging off the housing and no rupture disk was in place beneath the assembly. Additionally, there was no required surge protection on the rupture disk assembly. Enviroserve placed the appropriate rupture disk and resecured the assembly. The tank car was then held until the proper surge protection device could be placed in the assembly. Conrail and Enviroserve worked with the car owner and Steve Kuz, Alltrantec 519-718-8377 to secure the proper service equipment.  On October 4, 2023 the new surge protection device was installed on the tank car and it was released back into transportation.    Cause Code: 437 5 x ( 5 + 5 + 0 ) x ( 2+ 2 ) =  200&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2023100573</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
