<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for RI</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for RI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 12:29:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024080073</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024080073&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-08-23T15:14:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-08-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: FORT LAUDERDALA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: RI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED AIRLINES HOLDINGS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Customer in 36F Approached the aft lav and informed us that his cell phone charging unit battery&amp;quot;had expanded and broke out of the case&amp;quot;. I asked him to bring it to us while I retrieved the TCB. He brought it to the cdt galley where FA Vanak took pictures and went to the front to share them with the purser and captain. I placed the unit temporarily in the TCB without breaking the seal awaiting further instructions and checking the eFAOM. The unit was not hot or Ieaking. The Captain looked at the pictures and advised us to place in the TCB and monitor. I did so for the remaining 40 mins or so. We returned the battery to the passenger upon deplaning and advised him to dispose of it properly. We were advised by MX that since we did not need to break the seal on the zipper Of the TCB it could be returned to its stowed position.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024080073</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
