<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for WV</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for WV</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 09:13:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040079</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040079&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-05T15:11:25+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-01&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BECKLEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WV&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: TAPE CAME LOOSE ON PACKAGE, EMPLOYEE NOTICED IT WAS A CAN OF SPRAY PAINT IN BOX WITH NO SHIPPING PAPERS OR DIAMOND LABELS&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040079</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024040064</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024040064&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-05T15:11:25+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SOUTH CHARLESTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WV&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: VEOLIA ES TECHNICAL SOLUTIONS, L.L.C.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: A Veolia employee was driving a box truck loaded with a pair of totes and 15-20 55 gallon drums. Everything had been secured prior to leaving the customer&amp;#x27;s site with ratchet straps utilizing the e-track system in the truck. The road leaving the customer site grades down hill and as the driver was coming down hill he felt the load shift in the truck. The driver stopped at the stop sign at the bottom of the hill and exited the truck only to find that there was material leading from the front side of the truck cargo box. The totes had shifted and pulled the e-track away from the side of the truck, broke the clip that goes into the e-track, and slid forward in the cargo area of the truck, pushing a pallet jack into a poly drum filled with mostly water with trace amount of solvent. A corner of the pallet jack punched a hole in the poly drum releasing the contents out into the truck cargo area which left the truck and spilled on the road.   The Veolia driver called the local Fire Department to respond to the spill. WV DEP was on scene along with a third party ER group to clean up the material left on the road. The road was closed both directions for a period of time until clean up of the road and berm soil were complete. Note that after further investigation the drum that was damaged was over 96% water with trace amounts of organic compounds. This was not an RQ release that required reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024040064</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
