<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for WY</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for WY</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:11:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040867</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040867&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-22T15:11:57+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CASPER&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: package was unloaded from the trailer and the loader noticed there was a leak coming from the package.  the package was set aside and put into a tote where one of the management staff did an inspection. DescribePack: of the four containers of the disinfectant. the cap on one of the containers had come off from the top of it. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: better acknowledgement and loading of packages with hazardous marking on them.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040867</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024040415</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024040415&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-19T15:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SHERIDAN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SKYWEST AIRLINES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SkyWest Airlines was notified via an Irregular Operations Report of a PED fire/incident that occurred on SkyWest 5079 SHR-DEN on 3/30/24 (CRJ 200/N465SW).  The incident occurred prior to boarding in SHR. A passenger’s checked bag was loaded into the cargo pit. The ramp agent loading the bags inside the pit noticed smoke coming from the passenger’s bag. The bag was immediately removed from the aircraft and taken to a safe location.  Airport Fire and Rescue was notified and responded. Fire rescue crews neutralized the smoking bag. The passenger was then brought into a private room to speak with TSA and the station’s supervisor on duty to discuss the battery fire. According to the IOR report, it was determined, at that point, that the cause of the smoke was a charger charging what appears to be a battery tray holding possibly four 18650 lithium Ion Batteries. The charred battery/charging device is currently being held by the Airport Fire and Rescue in SHR.  I asked the station manager if he could tell if it was a charging device actively charging a battery in the checked bag. The best he could tell, because of the charred nature of the devices, that there may have been a e-cigarette charger that was possibly charging batteries.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024040415</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
