<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for KY</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for KY</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 18:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010769</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010769&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-07T15:11:14+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: INDEPENDENCE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: KY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: QA was called to pick up a wet hazmat on the dock. QA admin picked up hazmat and put hazmat into a lined tote. Only a small spot on outer package was wet from leaking bottle inside of hazmat, nothing leaked onto floor of dock that needed cleaned up. DescribePack: Cap came loose during handling causing internal leakage. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Cap was tightened and package was kept in a lined tote.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010769</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010520</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010520&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-06T18:12:07+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LOUISVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: KY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: AT THE UPS WORLDPORT FACILITY IN LOUISVILLE, KY RESPONDED TO A PACKAGE THAT NEEDED TO BE REWRAPPED DUE TO ANOTHER PACKAGE LEAKING TIDE LIQUID DETERGENT IN THE FACILITY. UPON REWRAP INSPECTION OF THE CONTENTS DISCOVERED 6 X 16 OUNCE COLEMAN ALL-PURPOSE PROPANE CANISTERS. THERE ARE NO DANGEROUS GOODS MARKS OR LABELS ON THE OUTER BOX. THIS PACKAGE HAS NOT BEEN ACCEPTED FOR AIR OR TRANSPORTED IN THE AIR BY UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO. THERMAL LABEL SHIPPER NAME IS ONLY &amp;quot;A&amp;quot;. THIS PACKAGE WAS SHIPPED FROM MARYLAND USING UPS ACCOUNT NUMBER 469R69, AMAZON.COM.KYDC, INC., 1656 OLD GREENSBORO RD., KERNERSVILLE NC 27284-6855.  Supplemental Report: AT THE UPS WORLDPORT FACILITY IN LOUISVILLE, KY RESPONDED TO A PACKAGE THAT NEEDED TO BE REWRAPPED DUE TO ANOTHER PACKAGE LEAKING TIDE LIQUID DETERGENT IN THE FACILITY. UPON REWRAP INSPECTION OF THE CONTENTS DISCOVERED 6 X 16 OUNCE COLEMAN ALL-PURPOSE PROPANE CANISTERS. THERE ARE NO DANGEROUS GOODS MARKS OR LABELS ON THE OUTER BOX. THIS PACKAGE HAS NOT BEEN ACCEPTED FOR AIR OR TRANSPORTED IN THE AIR BY UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO. THERMAL LABEL SHIPPER NAME IS ONLY &amp;quot;A&amp;quot;. THIS PACKAGE WAS SHIPPED FROM MARYLAND USING UPS ACCOUNT NUMBER 469R69, AMAZON.COM.KYDC, INC., 1656 OLD GREENSBORO RD., KERNERSVILLE NC 27284-6855.SUPPLEMENTAL REPORT DUE TO INCORRECT PSN AND ID NUMBER ON PREVIOUSLY SUBMITTED 01 / 19/2024 REPORT. PREVIOUS REPORT CUSTOMER TRACKING NUMBER 41120, INCIDENT REPORT NUMBER X-2024010520, INCIDENT TRACKING NUMBER 885978.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010520</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2023120219</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2023120219&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-02T00:33:30+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-11-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LIVINGSTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: KY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CSX TRANSPORTATION, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 11/22/2023, at approximately 13:51 hours, CSX train M54121 derailed at milepost 00C 138.8.  As a result of the derailment two tank cars containing sulfur breached and released their contents which caught fire.  Additionally, an empty tank car, which last contained methanol, was determined to have breached.  Multiple other rail cars containing non-regulated materials also breached and released contents- some of which caught fire.  The shippers of hazardous materials (loaded and residue shipments) were notified via CHEMTREC (Report #2023-11-22-00172).  Multiple response contractors, as well as CSX Hazardous Materials Team personnel, were responded to the incident emergently.  CSX and contractor personnel contained the fire and releases, as well as remediated the environmental impact.   Due to air quality concerns from the fire, local responders recommended that residents in the area of the derailment site evacuate.  This recommended evacuation applied to a single residence shortly after the derailment occurred and continued to expand for several hours until it included the entire town of Livingston, KY.  On 11/23/2023, at 16:00 hours, response officials lifted the evacuation.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2023120219</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
