<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MN</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MN</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:34:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020892</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020892&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-27T18:13:01+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-02-01&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROGERS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: load side manager called out a damaged hazmat. HESS specialist responded and retrieved it in a lined tote, bringing it back to the damage area and placing it atop the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. DescribePack: one bottle leaked from the vented cap due to improper handling. DurationRel: 0 and MitigateEffect: placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020892</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 18:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020853</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020853&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-26T15:11:07+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-31&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROGERS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: the driver scanned the package with a code 10 due to suspected damage and removed it from the van. someone set it aside in a lined tote for QA. QA person placed a code 39 on it and brought it back to the damage area, moving it to the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. DescribePack: two jerricans leaked small amounts from the caps due to improper handling of package and resulted in dents to the sides of the jerricans. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020853</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 15:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020651</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020651&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-23T18:13:34+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROGERS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: HAP specialist noticed liquid droplets around the cap while processing the hazmat after its arrival. he checked the spillage and found that it was hydrogen peroxide. he placed the package carefully into a lined tote and had a coworker bring it to the damage area and place it atop the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. DescribePack: while the cap does not appear cracked or particularly loose, the spillage is coming from the cap itself somehow. minor stains appear on the arrow label below the cap. DurationRel: 0 and MitigateEffect: placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020651</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2023120020</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2023120020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-24T00:32:25+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-11-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SAINT PAUL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SOO LINE RAILROAD COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: At 13:15 on 11/05/2023 a 500 Line Railroad (DBA CPKC) Hazardous Materials Officer became aware that  UTLX 220854 was leaking from its protective housing at the CPKC St. Paul, MN rail yard. A railroad  qualified response contractor was mobilized to investigate. Upon arrival, responders identified that the release was emanating from the threads on the nipple,  where the liquid valve connects to the pressure plate. Responders could not tighten the valve  because the threads were cross threaded. Because of this, absorbents were placed in the protective  housing, around the leak to catch additional product and replaced daily. The shipper was notified,  and subsequently mobilized a Mobile Repair Unit (MRU) to repair the car. The MRU removed the  Nitrogen pad (5Ibs) that had been applied to the car at the time of shipping, which stopped the  leak. However, the MRU could not remove the liquid valve to repair the connection. Because of this, the Shipper applied for an OTMA to move the car to home shop. Both CPKC and UP  Railroads would not agree to this move, so the car was transferred and cleaned an purged in St.  Paul. Once this was done, CPKC and UP Railroads agreed to move the car under an OTMA-1 to home shop  for repairs. File Note: Item 19-the quantity released was estimated based on the best information available at  the time of filing. This shipment was offered as a &amp;#x27;bulk&amp;#x27; shipment, aka one car load, therefore the  exact amount offered in this package is not known to the carrier. This carrier does not have access to mass balance data which can exactly quantify this value.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2023120020</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
