<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for VA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for VA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 06:14:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2022090941</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2156653&gt;E-2022090941&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2156653&gt;E-2022090941&lt;/A"&gt;Report E-2022090941&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-07-26T00:36:22+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2022-09-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: RURAL RETREAT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: VA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ENVIRONMENTAL OPTIONS INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Environmental Options Inc (EOI) truck was en route to Environmental Enterprises Inc (EEI) in Marion VA with a load of hazardous waste.  The tractor became disabled on the shoulder of I-81 at MM 59.5  EOI contacted EEI to dispatch a tractor to the site, to pull the trailer to EEI Located in Marion VA.  When EEI arrived they discovered a liquid leaking out of the nose of the trailer and thought a chlorine Vapor was observed when checking the load.  EEI contacted  Leann Herman with EOI.  Ms. Herman then contacted the state police and First Call Environmental to respond to a hazmat incident.  Ms Herman then reached out to Elizabeth Lohman with the Office of Pollution Response &amp;amp; Emergency Preparedness with the VA DEQ. Due to the hazmat on board and response time of 3 hours for First Call, Scott Sproles the Regional Hazmat officer with VDEM was dispatched to the scene and called in Wythe County Emergency Services to help.  During this time the NRC, VEOC were also notified.  DEQ contacted VDOT to dispatch the Safety Patrol Operator to evaluate the need for traffic control and a lane closure was put into place.   The initial incident report to the NRC indicated chlorine tabs gassing off (Incident report 1346219).  Once Hazmat crew was on scene and the load was transferred to another trailer, a leaking drum of nitric acid nickel solution was discovered.  The drum had a small pin hole in the bottom of the drum causing the release .  The leaking drum was overpacked and spilled material was neutralized and collected in a drum for proper disposal.  Ms. Herman updated the NRC incident report to to show approximately 10 gallons of nitric acid nickel solution was released (Incident report 1346275).  A follow up call was made on 09/03/2022 to provide updated information of the clean up. The material on the ground was also neutralized and will be collected into a drum and taken for proper disposal Incident report 1346306.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2022090941</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
