<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for ME</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for ME</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:16:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040860</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040860&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-22T15:11:57+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LEWISTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ME&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: During a.m. sort, the driver brought the package over to the QA dept and reported it was leaking. This QA personnel placed the item in a tote to contain further leaking outside the package. Further investigation and a SDS was researched. DescribePack: The corners of the package were wet. Upon inspection the inside of the package was saturated. Two bottles each containing 1/2 gallon of epoxy hardener and resin were wet and most of the liquid was around the cap. The bottle of hardener felt lighter than the other container. Unable to determine the cause, when tipped over and examined there were no puncture holes. The liquid had hardened around the cap. The label on the bottles indicated it was hazardous. DurationRel: 3 and MitigateEffect: The driver brought the package over to the QA dept once observed it was leaking. It was then placed in a tote to contain the leaking. Once identified it was hazardous, it was placed in a red hazmat tote and the processing of the hazmat was initiated.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040860</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040567</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040567&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-18T18:14:13+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-01&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LEWISTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ME&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: The package was discovered at the re-pack area at this station. It was brought over to the QA dept for further inspection. The bottom edge was saturated and the closures were open where the package was wet. A search via Spidr indicated it was not in its original packaging and was repacked at the Hart HUB. The contents were researched and examined and found to be leaking. An SDS was obtained and found to be hazardous. The item and its packaging was then placed in a haardous tote and processed as a damaged hazmat. DescribePack: The bottom of the package was wet and open. Inside there were three plastic containers with plastic tape placed over the caps and all three were placed in a plastic bag within the package. The image on Spidr indicates the package was originally larger and totaling 49.00pounds and only had a label indicating it was fragile. One of the three containers conaining cyco platinum ph up had significant volumn missing due to a loose cap that was leaking when the container was flipped upside down. DurationRel: 4 and MitigateEffect: The package was placed in a hazmat tote once it was  discovered that it was hazardous. Proper PPE was donned, and the processing of a damaged hazmat was initiated.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040567</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
