<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for ME</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for ME</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 03:16:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024080905</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024080905&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-08-19T21:12:43+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-08-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SACO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ME&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Federal Express Corporation&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 1 gallon adhesive in plastic bag placed in a used box stuffed full of plastic. paint clips pooped and adhesive leaked into bag. the smell was the give away that it had leaked. no visible damage shown on box&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024080905</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 21:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024080642</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024080642&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-08-14T15:13:37+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-08-07&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SACO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ME&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 4 1 gallon bottles in box with no partitions or protective packaging. caps loosened and pressure made seal under cap peel up a bit and a small amount leaked out of 3 bottles&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024080642</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024080676</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024080676&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-08-13T15:14:07+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-08-06&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LEWISTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ME&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: The package was discovered while offloading the first inbound trailer of the day during the start of pre-load sort at around 3:15am wet/leaking.  The package was then placed into a line bin &amp;amp; brought to QA for processing.  Upon inspecting the packages exterior, the shipping label had a &amp;quot;No-Air&amp;quot; marking underneath the ground symbol, &amp;amp; and a slip that contained a Safety Data Sheet for the contents inside was found on one side of the box.  It was also discovered that the package did not have any Hazmat/Hazmat paperwork &amp;amp;/or Limited Quantity markings on the package which raised some concerns.  Upon opening the package 4 1-gallon cans of Seal For Life Industries Temper Kote 1000 41 Silver Industrial Heat Coating were found soiled &amp;amp; with the lids popped off causing them to leak contents.  3 out of 4 were also badly bent/dented &amp;amp; crushed on several areas of the can.  None of the 4 cans had paint clips to help prevent the lids from popping off &amp;amp; no packing material was inside the package to protect the cans exteriors. According to Spidr image the package appeared to be unharmed when viewing overhead images of the package at MIDD hub, meaning the package may have loaded improperly &amp;amp; damaged in transit as a result.  When referencing Section 14 under DOT classification in the Safety Data Sheet it was discovered the contents are classified as Packing Group 2 &amp;amp; as a Class 3 Flammable Liquid.  Several packages were leaked on as a result of the spill but were able to be successfully repacked.  The portion of the leftover cardboard from the repacks were held at the QA cage to be placed into the line salvage drum per cleanup.  The Improper Shipping Form &amp;amp; Damaged Package Report were filled out.  Contents &amp;amp; cardboard were placed into a line salvage drum &amp;amp; sealed.  Large rubber green gloves &amp;amp; blue nitrile examination gloves were used when handing the hazardous material &amp;amp; an additional line bin was used as a precautionary measure.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024080676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
