<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for NM</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for NM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:32:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2023090114</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2196434&gt;I-2023090114&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2196434&gt;I-2023090114&lt;/A"&gt;Report I-2023090114&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-10-12T00:30:42+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-04-10&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City:  Caprock&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: COASTAL TRANSPORT CO., INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: The cargo tank motor vehicle(CTMV) was traveling on highway 380 near mile marker 200. The CTMV experienced a tire blow out on axle four, passenger side tire. The driver was unable to stop safely as the one lane each direction roadway contained no improved or paved shoulder for emergency stops. The driver was forced to travel approximately 1.5 miles at slow speed before the driver could slowly stop at a roadside pull out. The skidding tire overheated and Ignited with flames. After stopping, the driver used the on board fire extinguisher In attempt to extingulsh the fire. The flames quickly grew and ignited the product hoses slowed on the equipment tray that is mounted on the passenger side, below the cargo compartments. The fire/heat quickly melted through the aluminum shell of the cargo compartments. As the compartment shells melted through, the flammable liquid ignited. The fire consumed the cargo tank motor vehicle(truck tractor/semi-trailer) and product. The Caprock volunteer fire department contained the blaze and allowed the product to be consumed by the fire. Approximately 150 gallons of diesel fuel remained in the bottom of the compartment shell after the fire was extinguished. This product was picked up and disposed of by the local HM response vendor that was called to the scene. The vehicle wreckage was loaded onto a flatbed semi-trailer and carried away for disposal. The HM response vendor scraped and cleaned the pavement area.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2023090114</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
