<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MS</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MS</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:56:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030470</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030470&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-04-15T00:53:32+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-07&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: RICHLAND&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 8000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: At 02:08 EST on 3/7, Tony Hobson with XPO-LJS contacted ERTS to report a spill of about 2 quarts of an unidentified material onto the trailer floor from a pallet of boxes. The pallet was poorly loaded and damaged in transit from XDM. The material cannot be identified as the pallet is wrapped in opaque shrink wrap, and ERTS advised the terminal not to handle the material as it is a regulated corrosive. ERTS will dispatch a contractor to assist. Contractors arrived onsite and confirmed approximately 2-gallons of UN2491 Hood &amp;amp; Flue Cleaner Concentrate product released to a 2’x3’ area of the trailer floor and small amount to the concrete floor due to a forklift puncture. The crew found (2) boxes damaged, each containing (4) ½ gallon jugs each. The crew cleaned up the spill with citric acid. The cardboard, damaged poly jugs, waste product, oil-dri, citric acid and PPE were containerized into (1) 55-gallon poly drum. The waste was staged onsite for terminal personnel to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030470</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
