<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for VA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for VA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 21:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024030485</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024030485&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-18T15:10:48+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-06&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ASHLAND&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: VA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Upon unloading a trailer the OPS Manager noticed the Hazmat package laying on it&amp;#x27;s side and discoloration on packaging due to it being wet. OPS Manager called for QA and QA placed the pkg in a hazmat container and into the hazmat cage. Upon inspection of the hazmat it was found that because of the package laying on it&amp;#x27;s side it caused pressure on one of the bottles causing it to leak slowly through the packaging. DescribePack: Closure of the bottle loosened a little due to pressure from being lain on it&amp;#x27;s side. DurationRel: 15 and MitigateEffect: QA Hazmat personnel placed the package into a hazmat container right side up to stop leaking.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024030485</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024030231</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024030231&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-14T18:15:01+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-01&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROANOKE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: VA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: When the contents were discovered being coded for a refusal at the station for being damaged, we discovered that the contents (Which were 2 2.5-gallon jugs of liquid machine detergent which was a hazmat under UN 1760 Corrosive liquids N.O.S. Technical name Sodium Hydroxide) have leaked a small amount of the contents out of the package. Some of the box is wet due on the exterior but that is rain that has soaked a portion of the packaging. Upon closure inspection the caps were loose, and the corrosive liquids were observed to originate at the affected area. None of the liquid contents from inside of the package has been released out of the box, but still leaked from the inner jugs. No inner packing was found inside of the package. DescribePack: The Jugs were observed to have no leaks upon discovery, but some of the liquid inside of the container was out of the container and was at the time of discovery staining the inner exterior box. The caps enclosing the jugs containing the corrosive solution were observed to be loose with the most recently escaped liquid appearing right below the cap. The caps on the containers were promptly tightened and no leaks were observed after test and observing for a leak. DurationRel: 3 and MitigateEffect: Upon awareness of the damaged hazmat, the caps were tightened prevent any further leaks.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024030231</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024021322</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024021322&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-18T15:10:48+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-02-07&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: HAMPTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: VA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 2/6/2024 at approximately 1830, Dangerous Goods Administration received a call from Employee 4346935 is the station location in Hampton, reporting an undeclared dangerous goods shipment.  The package consisted of one fiberboard box, containing an inner fiberboard box with a glass bottle inside.  The attached paperwork identifies the commodity as &amp;quot;Hydrogen Sulfide&amp;quot;, prompting the opening of the shipment for verification.  The package was not prepared with the required DG markings, labeling, or paperwork, in accordance with IATA regulations and is being held, pending an FAA investigation.  UPDATE:  Further review revealed a misclassification of the commodity.  The commodity appears to be identified as &amp;quot;fuel oil&amp;quot; and as requesting that test be conducted using &amp;quot;hydrogen sulfide&amp;quot;.  The spill incident is being resubmitted with the updated classification.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024021322</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024030030</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024030030&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-14T18:15:01+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-02-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Charlottesville&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: VA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: BUCKINGHAM BRANCH RAILROAD&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Please see attachment&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024030030</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024030014</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024030014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-12T15:28:43+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-02-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Lynchburg&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: VA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CLI TRANSPORT, LP&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Company Fuel Driver was making a fuel delivery at store at 09:03am, the driver had two hoses of connected from the trailer belly valves to the underground fuel storage tank(UST). Cones were in place to protect the area as well as lights activated for warnings. A white pickup truck(Super Duty) bearing Maryland registration# 9EC0549, pulling a - cement mixer trailer, disregarded the activated lights and orange security cones of our vehicle; drove over the hose fitting connected to the UST and tore the fitting and the lip of the UST off the tank. The hose attached to the trailer UST became stuck under the pickup truck. The driver exited their truck and removed the hose from under his truck; and left the scene immediately. Police report was filed with VA State Police(Trooper J.B. Moore) for truck&amp;quot;leaving th€ scene of the accident&amp;quot;. Fuel driver managed to capture a photo of the truck that ran over the fitting and hoses and reported the incident to Law Enforcement and the Safety Department immediately. Material spilled was contained by the fuel driver using absorbent pads, and emptied the remaining fuel in the hose into the UST. No fuel contaminated the ground nor entered into any water systems.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024030014</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
