<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for LA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for LA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 18:18:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024110505</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024110505&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-19T12:23:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: HARAHAN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Illinois Central Railroad Company&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 18091&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 10-24-2024 at approximately 07:00 AM a CN transportation employee observed a white vapor emitting from the top of tank car # RCRX 2542 (residue/UN 1789/Class 8/PGII) while performing switching operations at the CN Mays Yard in Harahan, LA. The car was set out to an isolation track. All departments were notified leading to an emergency response from a CN Dangerous Goods Team contractor. The responding contractor observed a small amount of liquid (PH tested ?1?) within the protective housing. All securement nuts on the air and liquid valve were verified to be tool tight. There was no obvious point of the leak during the initial inspection. The tank car was pressurized with dry air to 10 psi for the purpose of identifying the exact origin of the leak. The pressure test revealed a minuscule leak emanating from the spool of the liquid eduction line through what appeared to be a pin sized hole. The tank car was completely de-pressurized through a scrubbing media. The pinhole on the spool was wrapped with chemical tape to prevent any further leakage. The car owner was notified of the findings and will send a qualified mobile repair unit out to replace the spool and re-qualify the tank car. 10-31-2024 the tank car owner performed an assessment of the tank car. Below is their findings: Technicians from our Saint Gabreil, LA certified shop responded to RCRX 2542 on 10/31/2024.  Upon arrival, the technician&amp;#x27;s initial inspection found product residue inside the protective housing.  In addition, there appeared to be no gasket present below the product blind flange which was confirmed after removing the blind flange.  A product gasket was applied and secured.  The car was then pressurized to 30 psi and a certified leak test was performed to all fittings and connections with no leaks found.   The residue product was rinsed off of the fittings and side of car.  Security seals were applied as well to the fittings.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024110505</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
