<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for AR</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for AR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:13:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024071917</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024071917&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-07-26T18:15:58+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-07-16&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LITTLE ROCK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: RESPONDER WAS CALLED TO A LEAKING PACKAGE AT UNLOAD SECTION ON BAY# 4 ON THE TWILIGHT SORT. RESPONDER PICKED UP A LEAKING CORROSIVE HAZ MAT IN THE TRAILER. RESPONDER PLACED THE LEAKING PACKAGE AND ALL CONTAMINATED MATERIAL IN A SPILL TRAY FOLLOWING PROPER DECISION TREE AND CORROSIVE RESPONSE SHEET. DAMAGE PACKAGE WAS TAKEN TO DMP PROCESSING CENTER FOR FURTHER PROCESSING.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024071917</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024070016</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024070016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-07-25T15:13:18+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BENTONVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: REPUBLIC AIRWAYS HOLDINGS INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Passenger purchased gas generator at a Lowes in New Jersey on 5/27/2024 in an effort to use for disaster relief in Northwest Arkansas. She was under the impression that the unit was new because it was packaged that way and she had no reason to believe otherwise. There were no fumes or noticeable stains on the box. She presented it to the American Airlines ticket counter in PHL for her AA 4602/4342 PHL-LGA-XNA flights operated by Republic Airways, Inc. TSA scanned the item in PHL before being loaded on the aircraft and no dangerous goods were present. Ground crew in PHL loaded it on the aircraft. The unit shipped to LGA and no noticeable spills or fumes were observed by LGA ground crew and the package continued to XNA. Once in XNA ground crew noticed approximately 1 qt leaked on the cargo floor and some luggage. Republic Ops, Maintenance and Dangerous Goods were contacted immediately. On call maintenance contractors for Republic Airways were called out and cleaned the aircraft quickly with several cleaning agents. The extent of gasoline spilled on the cargo floor was minimal.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024070016</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
