<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for NM</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for NM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 03:14:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040756</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040756&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-22T15:11:57+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROSWELL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: The package was was found on the floor on the driver side of nose. The orientation arrows were not followed. Package was removed from trailer 819655, The package handler that carried the package to the NC belt was not aware that the package was leaking. When the package handler that found the leaking hazmat had relayed that the package was leaking. The hazmat package was on the vertical belt being transfer to the NC belt. The package handler had carried the leaking hazmat to NC belt even though it was communicated. Operations were stopped while  in-house cleanup was preformed. DescribePack: The body of the container was cracked along the side with a 1cm line. DurationRel: 0 and MitigateEffect: Response from ops supervisor to perform inhouse cleanup.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040756</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040934</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040934&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-19T15:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ALBUQUERQUE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 1.X-2024040934 SequenceEvent: Package was found leaking on the belts and then immediately brought to QA. DescribePack: The lid to the bottle of liquid came loose causing it to leak. DurationRel: 2 and MitigateEffect: Package was placed in the spill containment area upon discovery.   2. X-2024040978 SequenceEvent: A leaking package was brought to QA, upon inspection it was found it has a loose cap. It was found that it was undeclared hazmat. DescribePack: The lid came loose causing leakage. DurationRel: 2 and MitigateEffect: Package was brought to containment container by QA.   3. X-2024040979 SequenceEvent: Package was found leaking on the belts and then immediately brought to QA. DescribePack: The lid to the bottle of liquid came loose causing it to leak. DurationRel: 2 and MitigateEffect: Package was placed in the spill containment area upon discovery.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040934</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040641</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040641&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-17T15:16:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SANTA TERESA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: PACKAGE HANDLER NOTIFIED MANAGER OF HAZMET AND AFTER SEEING THAT IT WAS WET HE PUT IT IN A RED TOT AND BROUGHT IT TO THE HAZMAT CAGE AND SPOKE TO QA FOR INSPECTION. DescribePack: Their WAS A CRACK ALONG THE SEAM OF THE INNER HANDLE OF TWO OF THE BOTTLES. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: WE PUT DOWN ABSORBENT PADS AROUND THE AREA TO PICK UP ANY LIQUIDE FROM THE FLOOR.THE BOX WAS PLACED IN A RED TOT AND BROUGHT TO THE HAZMAT CAGE AND WRAPPED UP IN A PLASTIC BAG.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040641</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
