<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for AK</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for AK</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 03:11:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2023070026</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2187639&gt;E-2023070026&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2187639&gt;E-2023070026&lt;/A"&gt;Report E-2023070026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-07-22T00:38:22+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-06-06&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Coldfoot&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A specification cargo tank 1,000 gallons or greater containing any hazardous materials that (1) received structural damage to the lading retention system or damage that requires repair to a system int&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: WEAVER BROS., INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: A semi tractor was driving northbound on the Dalton Highway around Mile 126, approaching a curve that is colloquially referred to among Alaskan truck drivers as &amp;quot;Oh Shit Corner&amp;quot;.  The driver entered the corner at excessive speed, and immediately before the corner struck a large pothole in the road, which apparently caused two trailer tires to blow out, contributing to the loss of control in the corner.  The tractor trailer combination rolled onto its side and departed the roadway, coming to rest beside and below the highway grade.  The driver received only minor injuries and did not require transport for medical attention.  At the time of the initial response, Alaska Commercial Vehicle Compliance and Alaska State Troopers believed there may have been a release due to the odor, however Suburban Propane (shipper) personnel arrived on the scene and reported there was no leak beyond normal vent operation.  Personnel and equipment were mobilized to the scene, the product was transloaded into another tanker, and a wrecker removed the tractor and trailer and brought them back to Fairbanks.  Professional traffic control allowed this to be completed without requiring a road closure.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2023070026</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
