<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for AK</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for AK</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 03:43:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025031021</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025031021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-26T21:14:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: JNU&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ALASKA AIRLINES, INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Undeclared hazmat found during screening.  Other undeclared hazmat found with no release as follows. (Replicating questions 14-29) ALCOHOLS, N.O.S. (ETHANOL)//haz class 3 // UN 1987//not shipped as hazardous waste//not toxic by inhalation//not shipped under Exemption, Approval, or CA number//shipment was undeclared with no release//packaging type non-bulk/outer packaging plastic box//Aerosols, flammable//haz class 2.1 // UN 1950 //not shipped as hazardous waste//not toxic by inhalation//not shipped under Exemption, Approval, or CA number//shipment was undeclared with no release//packaging type non-bulk/outer packaging plastic box// petroleum distillates, N.O.S // haz class 3 // UN 1268 //not shipped as hazardous waste//not toxic by inhalation//not shipped under Exemption, Approval, or CA number//shipment was undeclared with no release//packaging type non-bulk/outer packaging plastic box      AWB71913015 arrived from AS66/12. One piece, a blue cooler fell on the ramp and because the lid wasn&amp;#x27;t taped or anything like that, the lid opened, and its contents were spilled out. It was then that some aerosol cans and a chargeable lithium battery were discovered. The runner brought it over to the warehouse and alerted me to take a look. I was able to pull the contents out of the cooler and found more undeclared DG. There was a tote that was a part of the six lot, so I opened it up to see what was in it and discovered a lot of batteries and lighters. Pictures of everything found and all sides of each piece are attached.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025031021</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025031020</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025031020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-26T21:14:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANCHORAGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: attachment Name:771497454989-2.jpg&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025031020</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025031019</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025031019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-26T21:14:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANCHORAGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 5 fibreboard boxes containing undeclared perfume. 4 boxes with 28 bottles and 1 box with 29 bottles. no release.  held onsite for FAA inspection.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025031019</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025030044</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025030044&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-26T21:14:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-03&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANCHORAGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Everts Air Cargo&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 55000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Undeclared hazmat shipment of Lithium Batteries. 5760 used computers from bush Alaska to a  re-seller via Anchorage Alaska. Lower Kuskokwim School District (LKSD) engaged with Second Life Mac (SLM)(a company from Skokie,  IL) for them to buy their used computers, and provide all services to package and transport them.  Because of the very remote location of the computers (Bethel, AK), the LKSD followed SLM&amp;#x27;s  instructions to package and deliver to the airline. SLM instructed LKSD to not mark or label any of the packages, and to cover them under black shrink  wrap, deliver to the airline, and the airline agent would take care of everything. Neither the  Airline nor Airline Agent knew anything about this shipment. 5 pallets of these items were tendered  to the Airline in Bethel, AK, and described by the shipper on our AWB as &amp;quot;ELECTRONICS&amp;quot;. Shipper was  asked if there were any hazardous materials in the shipment, and shipper answered NO. Shipper  signed the Airline&amp;#x27;s AWB and initialed that there was no hazardous materials in the shipment.  5  pallets were flown from Bethel to Anchorage, AK, consignee notified 3 times without picking the  freight up, and after 3 weeks, Airline contacted the Shipper and asked what to do with the  shipment? Shipper contacted the Consignee, and they then responded that day, and arrived the next day on  sight with marking and labeling to further move these pallets on FedEx. They applied the hazmat  dimond label to the 5 pallets while on our ramp.  It had rained, and some of the boxes got wet,  soaking some contents in water, which initiated a damage freight claim process.  No action was  taken on the claim, because of two issues: one-freight charges have not been paid for, two-shipment  was abandoned for three weeks with no communication from consignee. On March 5th, Airline was  notified of a demand letter from a lawyer for a claimed damage amount.  The demand letter was  elevated to airline administration, and was the first time administration became aware of the hidden hazmat  shipment. SLM has a third party involved, Jesse Carnahan with Lynx Enterprises (Wasilla, AK). The Airline does not know how much of or who is responsible for what between Lynx and SLM. Once administration became aware of the non-declared hazmat, an investigation ensued which led to this 5800.1 report. No release or damage to the lithium batteries has been declared.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025030044</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025030831</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025030831&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-22T21:13:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-14&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANCHORAGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: AT THE UPS FACILITY IN ANCHORAGE, ALASKA, ONE PACKAGE BECAME WET FROM RAINWATER REQUIRING A REWRAP. THE PACKAGE HAD PREVIOUSLY FLOWN FROM ONT TO ANC USING GROUND TO ALASKA RATE SERVICE WHICH MOVES IN THE AIR NETWORK. UPON INSPECTION OF THE CONTENTS DISCOVERED AN INNER BOX MARKED AND LABELED UN1070 NITROUS OXIDE WITH CLASS 2.2 AND 5.1 DIAMOND LABELS. THIS INNER BOX CONTAINED FOUR NITROUS OXIDE CYLINDERS. THERE WERE TWO ADDITIONAL LOOSE NITROUS OXIDE CYLINDERS IN THE BOX ALSO. THERE ARE NO DANGEROUS GOODS MARKS OR LABELS ON THE OUTER BOX. THIS PACKAGE WAS SHIPPED FROM WASHINGTON USING UPS ACCOUNT NUMBER J21R10, FULFILLMENT CENTER, 11815 TECHNOLOGY LN, FISHERS IN 46038-2890.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025030831</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
