<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:22:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025011283</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025011283&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-04T06:26:27+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SOMERVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: RESPONDED TO AN AIR STYROFOAM PACKAGE THAT WAS COLD TO THE TOUCH AND HEARD THE SOUND OF SOMETHING ROLLING AROUND INSIDE THE BOX. UPON INSPECTION OF THE CONTENTS DISCOVERED LESS THAN ONE POUND OF DRY ICE PELLETS COOLING DNA SAMPLES FOR RESEARCH. THERE ARE NO DANGEROUS GOODS MARKS OR LABELS ON THE OUTER BOX TO INDICATE DRY ICE WAS BEING USED TO COOL THE DNA SAMPLES. THE TRACKING NUMBER APPEARS TO HAVE BEEN USED ONCE ALREADY FOR A PREVIOUS BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS TO EUGENE, OREGON SHIPMENT IN JANUARY 2025. THIS PACKAGE IS A RETURN SERVICE PACKAGE THAT WAS SHIPPED FROM BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS ON 28-JAN-2025 USING UPS ACCOUNT NUMBER 863W29, PLASMIDSAURUS, 1850 MILLRACE DR SUITE 200, EUGENE OR 97403-2095. THIS PACKAGE HAS NOT BEEN ACCEPTED FOR AIR OR TRANSPORTED IN THE AIR BY UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025011283</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
