<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for NJ</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for NJ</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 03:12:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020133</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020133&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-12T18:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-02-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EDISON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: A BUBBLE MAILER CAME DOWN THE SORT OPEN. PACKAGE WAS GIVEN TO A RESPONDER WHO FOUND ONE X 12 OUNCE CONTAINER OF EXTREMELY FLAMMABLE ZIPPO LIGHTER FLUID. THERE ARE NO DANGEROUS GOODS MARKS OR LABELS ON THE OUTER BUBBLE MAILER. THIS PACKAGE HAS NOT BEEN ACCEPTED FOR AIR OR TRANSPORTED IN THE AIR BY UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020133</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020451</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020451&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-16T00:33:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: DURING THE OVERNIGHT SORT THE PACKAGE ARRIVED AT THE HAZMAT CAGE SHOWING OBVIOUS SIGNS OF INTERNAL LEAKAGE. UPON INSPECTION ONE BOTTLE OF FOUR RAPICIDIE WAS FOUND FULLY LEAKED OUT. THE REMAINING CONTENTS WERE PLACED IN A SALVAGE DRUM TO BE RETURN TO SHIPPER UNLESS OTHERWISE. DescribePack: FAILURE OF PACKAGE CAUSED FROM A LOOSE CAP BECAUSE THE PACKAGE WAS DROPPED OR MISHANDLED. DurationRel: 24 and MitigateEffect: THE REAMINING CONTENTS WERE PLACED IN A SALVAGE DRUM TO AWAIT DISPOSITION.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020451</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020247</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020247&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-16T00:33:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: DURING THE OVERNIGHT SORT THE PACKAGE ARRIVED AT THE HAZMAT CAGE SHOWING INTERNAL LEAKAGE. UPON INSPECTION TWO (2) BOTTLES OF RAPICIDE (PART A) WAS FOUND WITH SLIGHT LEAKAGE, ALSO 2 BOTTLES WERE MISSING (PART B). THE REMAINING CONTENTS WERE PLACED IN A SALVAGE DRUM TO BE RETURN TO SHIPPER UNLESS OTHERWISE. DescribePack: FAILURE OF RAPICIDE CAUSED FROM THE PACKAGE BEING MISHANDLED OR DROPPED. DurationRel: 8 and MitigateEffect: THE REMAINING CONTENTS WERE PLACED IN A LINED SALVAGED DRUM TO AWAIT DISPOSITION.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020247</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020257</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020257&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-16T00:33:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-10&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: TRENTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Package became wet from rain during transit and upon inspection it was noticed that powder was leaking from the top. Package was immediately put into a red bin and secured in the hazmat cage. DescribePack: Product was leaking from top. Lid was no longer connected to drum properly. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Package was immediately put into a red bin and secured in the hazmat cage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020257</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020301</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020301&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-16T00:33:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: TRENTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Shipping box crushed and torn while in transit causing Alkyd Traffic Marking Paint 1Gal can to have loose lid.  Package was immediately placed in RED Tote upon discovery and brought to HAZMAT Cage for further processing. DescribePack: Shipping box crushed and torn while in transit causing Alkyd Traffic Marking Paint 1Gal can to have loose lid. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Package was immediately placed in RED Tote upon discovery and brought to HAZMAT Cage for further processing.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020301</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020302</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020302&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-16T00:33:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: TRENTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Shipping box crushed and torn while in transit causing three of four ReliaChem Smokehouse Cleaner Heavy Duty Foaming Cleaner 1Gal bottles to have loose caps.  Package was immediately placed in RED Tote and brought to HAZMAT Cage for further processing. DescribePack: Shipping box crushed and torn while in transit causing three of four ReliaChem Smokehouse Cleaner Heavy Duty Foaming Cleaner 1Gal bottles to have loose caps. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Package was immediately placed in RED Tote and brought to HAZMAT Cage for further processing.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020302</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020311</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020311&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-16T00:33:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Package was discovered leaking by the driver upon his return to the station after completing the pickup. Package was placed into a salvage drum to contain the spillage. DescribePack: UPON INSPECTION OF INNER CONTENTS DURING THE TWILIGHT SHIFT 2X5 LITERS (PLASTIC BOTTLES) RAPICIDE PA HIGH LEVEL DISINFECTANT PART A AND 2X5 LITERS (PLASTIC BOTTLES) RAPICIDE PA HIGH LEVEL DISINFECTANT PART B ONE HAD A LOOSE CAP CAUSING LEAKAGING ALLOWING 20 OUNCES OF SPILLAGE FROM THE BOTTLE. WHICH ALSO CAUSED DAMAGE TO THE OUTER PACKAGING AS WELL. DurationRel: 8 and MitigateEffect: FACILITY PROCEDURES FOR DAMAGED HAZARDOUS MATERIAL FOLLOWED, CONTENTS CONTAINED AND AWAITING DISPOSITION.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020311</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020459</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020459&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-16T00:33:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-23&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BARRINGTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: PACKAGE WAS UNLOADED FROM THE TRUCK AND IT WAS NOTICED THE BOX WAS WET.  PACKAGE WAS TAKEN TO THE HAZMAT CAGE, SECURED AND REPACKED IN A SALVAGE DRUM. DescribePack: 1 GALLON HAD A LOOSE CAP AND LEAKED OUT APPROXIMATELY .25 CUP OF LIQUID.  2 OF THE GALLONS HAD SOILED LABELS. DurationRel: 3 and MitigateEffect: PACKAGE WAS TAKEN TO THE HAZMAT CAGE, SECURED AND REPACKED IN A SALVAGE DRUM.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020459</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020496</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020496&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-15T12:17:17+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-23&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: During the overnight sort the package arrived at the hazmat cage showing obvious sign of internal leakage. Upon inspection 2 bottles of Part B Rapidcide was missing. The remaining contents were placed in a salvage drum with a clear hazmat bag awaiting to be returned to the shipper unless otherwise. DescribePack: Failure of Rapicide part B caused from the package being dropped or mishandled. DurationRel: 24 and MitigateEffect: Box was placed in a hazmat clear bag to await disposition.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020496</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020486</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020486&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-15T12:17:17+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-23&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 1. X-2024020486 SequenceEvent: During the overnight sort the package arrived at the hazmat cage showing obvious signs of internal leakage. Upon inspection 1 bottle of zep clog attack was found slightly leaking. The remaining contents were placed in a salvage drum to be returned to the shipper unless otherwise. DescribePack: Failure of zep clog attack was caused from it being dropped from mishandled. DurationRel: 12 and MitigateEffect: The contents were placed in a lined salvage drum to await disposition.   2. X-2024020494 SequenceEvent: During the overnight sort the package arrived to the hazmat cage. Upon inspection zep calcium, lime &amp;amp; rust stain remover box was found wet and the contents were missing. The box was placed in the hazmat cage in a hazmat clear bag to be scrapped or otherwise. DescribePack: Failure of zep calcium, lime &amp;amp; rust stain remover caused from the package being dropped or mishandled. DurationRel: 24 and MitigateEffect: Box was placed in a hazmat clear bag to await disposition.   3. X-2024020497 SequenceEvent: During the overnight sort the package arrived at the hazmat cage showing signs of internal leakage which caused to Fibreboard box to be damaged. Upon inspection 3 bottles of 4 Zep calcium, lime &amp;amp; rust stain remover have been damaged causing from loose caps. Remaining contents were placed in a salvage drum inside  clear hazmat bag. DescribePack: Failure of Zep Stain remover caused from the package being dropped or mishandled. DurationRel: 12 and MitigateEffect: Contents were placed in a savage drum to await disposition.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020486</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020253</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020253&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-15T12:17:17+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BARRINGTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: DURING THE UNLOAD THE MANAGER NOTICED THE SIDE OF THE BOX WAS REALLY DIRTY AND WET. THE MANAGER IMMEDICATELY TOOK SAID PACKAGE OVER TO THE HAZMAT CAGE TO SECURE IT AND VENTILATE IT PROPERLY. I WAS THEN CALLED OVER TO REPACK IT INTO A YELLOW SALVAGE DRUM SAFELY, SECURELY AND IN A TIMELY MANNER. APPROXIMATELY 1 CUP OF LIQUID LEAKED OUT OF ONE OF THE FOUR BOTTLES DUE TO THE BOTTLE HAVING A LOOSE CAP. IT LEAKED FROM THE PART A RAPICIDE BOTTLE. THE OTHER 3 BOTTLES WERE FINE, JUST A LITTLE WET FROM THE ALREADY LEAKAGE. DescribePack: THERE WERE 4 BOTTLES INSIDE THE PACKAGE. TWO OF THE PART A SOLUTION AND TWO OF THE PART B SOLUTION. ONE OF THE BOTTLES FROM THE PART A SOLUTION HAD A LOOSE CAP CAUSING APPROXIMATELY 1 CUP OF THE LIQUID TO LEAK OUT. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: THE MANAGER TAKING THE PACKAGE IMMEDIATELY OVER THE HAZMAT CAGE TO SECURE AND VENTILATE PROPERLY AND THEN CALLING ME OVER TO SAFELY REPACK THE PRODUCT INTO A YELLOW SALVAGE DRUM IN A TIMELY MANNER.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020253</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020213</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020213&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-15T12:17:17+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: DURING THE OVERNIGHT SORT THE PACKAGE WAS BROUGHT TO THE HAZMAT CAGE SHOWING OBVIOUS SIGNS OF INTERNAL LEAKAGE. UPON INSPECTION THREE (3) BOTTLES OF ZEP CALCIUM, LIME AND RUST STAIN REMOVER WAS FOUND. 1 BOTTLE WAS MISSING BUT THE CAP WAS PRESENT, THE REAMINING CONTENT WAS PLACED IN A SALVAGE DRUM. DescribePack: FAILURE OF  ZEP CALCIUM, LIME AND RUST STAIN REMOVER CAUSED FROM THE BOXBEING DROPPED OR MISHANDLED DurationRel: 4 and MitigateEffect: THE CONTENTS WERE PLACED IN A LINE SALVAGE DRUM TO AWAIT DISPOSITION.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020213</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024020226</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024020226&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-15T12:17:17+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: NORTH ARLINGTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDEX FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Associate did not block and/or brace freight properly for transport.  Freight was crushed causing release of product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024020226</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024020185</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024020185&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-15T12:17:17+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DELANCO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDEX FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Associate punctured freight with forklift blades while loading / unloading causing product to leak&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024020185</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020124</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020124&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-12T18:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-31&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: PARSIPPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: NO COMMENTS PROVIDED.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020124</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020125</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020125&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-12T18:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-31&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EDISON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SORTER NOTICED PACKAGE WAS LEAKING AND NOTIFIED SUPERVISOR. RESPONDER PROCESSED THROUGH DMP.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020125</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020123</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020123&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-12T18:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-31&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: MOUNT OLIVE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: HAZMAT BOX FOUND IN TRAILER WITH SMALL WET SPOT. LEAKING PACKAGE DECISION TREE AND HAZARDOUS RESPONSE SHEETS FOLLOWED BY RESPONDER AND PACKAGE PROCESSED IN THE DMP.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020123</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024020192</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024020192&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-12T18:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: DURING THE OVERNIGHT SORT I WAS CALLED TO THE QA AREA AND HANDED THE LABEL. THERE WERE NO ZEP CONTENTS IN SIGHT. THIS PACKAGE WILL BE SCRAPPED UNLESS OTHERWISE. DescribePack: FAILURE OF THE PACKAGE COULD CAUSE FROM THE PACKAGE BEING DROPPED OF MISHANDLED. DurationRel: 4 and MitigateEffect: I WILL BE AWAITING DISPOSITION.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024020192</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024020069</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024020069&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-12T18:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: FAIRFIELD&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: VEOLIA ES TECHNICAL SOLUTIONS, L.L.C.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On the morning of January 30, 2024, a Veolia employee was at the customer site loading a drum of sulfuric acid into their trailer when the incident occurred. The Veolia employee was maneuvering the drum to the edge of the dock, however there was no dock leveler or dock plate. The employee proceeded to get the drum cart and pick up and move the drum the rest of the way when one of the forks from the drum cart pierced the drum. The customer came to assist and pumped the damaged drum into a new drum. The damaged drum was then put into an overpack. The Veolia supervisor and EHS manager responded to assist by contacting the remediation/ spill response team to respond with a neutralizer so the truck can be cleaned up and the job can resume.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024020069</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010766</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010766&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-12T18:12:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KEASBEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Package arrived at hazmat during sunrise sort in plastic bin. DescribePack: Inspection showed package of &amp;quot;MEDIVATORS RAPICIDE PA&amp;quot; to be torn open, with 2 of 4 contents seperated and leaking. Damage most likely caused from being dropped or mishandled. DurationRel: 12 and MitigateEffect: Remaining contents will be returned to shipper in a salvage drum, unless otherwise stated.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010766</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
