<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for WY</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for WY</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:32:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024010458</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024010458&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-30T15:10:41+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROCK RIVER&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On January 18, 2024, at 0200 EST, an XPO Logistics tractor trailer hauling double trailers (truck # 05328716, trailer #s 03171129, 03171874) was involved in a rollover accident due to inclement weather conditions. Immediately after the accident occurred, the roads to the site were closed due to the weather and the unit was left onsite. No drains or waterways were reported to be impacted by the release. On January 18, 2024, at 0256 EST, XPO Logistics contacted Emergency Response and Training Solutions (ERTS) to manage and oversee the above referenced incident. ERTS secured Haz-Mat Response Inc. (HMRI) to perform emergency response and remediation. On January 18, 2024, HMRI responded to the site at 1140 ET to obtain an assessment of the site. At the time, there was no visual release of material from the unit, but it was also in 5-6” of snow. Once HMRI left site, the wrecker unit showed up at approximately 1300 ET to haul the unit offsite. Initially they did not report seeing a release of material when the unit was up righted. On January 19th, HMRI mobilized to the wrecker yard to find the batteries had released approximately 50-100 gallons of battery acid to the trailer floor, walls, ceiling, and soil along the passenger side of the unit in the wrecker yard. An estimated 5-gallons of acid impacted a 26’ x 1’ area of the soil in the dirt lot. Soda ash and floor dry were deployed to the impacted trailer floor to neutralize the acid. The wrecker crew then advise to HMRI there was a loss of acid to the incident site in the soil median where the unit came to a rest. HMRI secured the unit at the wrecker’s yard and mobilized to the accident site where they confirmed an approximate 2-gallon release to a 5’ x 15’ area of the median ditch. The area was hand excavated and all impacted soil placed into a drum which was removed from site. At this point, the 7-gallons of material confirmed to impact soil/dirt was reported to the WY DEQ. On January 22, 2024, at 1100 ET, HMRI returned to the wrecker yard to complete trailer remediation. Each battery was wiped down and inspected. All 70 salvageable batteries were secured on the unit on 4 pallets to be hauled back to XPO with the unit. The trailer floor was neutralized with soda ash and floor dry, and the soil was hand excavated. A total of 213 damaged batteries were containerized into (9) 95-gallon poly drums and will attempt to be recycled. All impacted debris including the impacted floor dry, soda ash, soil, dirt, poly sheeting, cardboard, and PPE were collected and containerized into (2) 55-gallon poly and (3) 95-gallon poly drums for disposal. All waste is currently located at HMRI’s shop located in Windsor, CO pending profiling, disposal, and recycling. Please see attached photos (Appendix 2).&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024010458</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 15:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
