<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MO</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MO</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 06:12:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010565</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010565&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-26T15:11:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EARTH CITY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: A FULLY LABELED HAZMAT PACKAGE THAT APPEARED TO BE LEAKING FROM THE CORNER OF THE BOX WAS DISCOVERED BY THE HVD PICKOFF ON THE PD 4. THE PICKOFF STOPPED THE BELT, SECURED IT, LOCKED IT, TESTED IT, THEN LEFT THE AREA AND NOTIFIED THE SUPERVISOR. WITHIN 5 MINUTES A DMP RESPONDER ARRIVED DONNING THE CORRECT PPE. USING THE DECISION TREE AND APPROPRIATE RESPONSE SHEET IT WAS DETERMINED THAT THE PACKAGE COULD BE SAFELY TRANSPORTED BACK TO THE DMP. UPON FURTHER INSPECTION IT WAS REVEALED THAT THE LID ON ONE OF THE PLASTIC 2.5 LITER INNER CONTAINERS WAS LOOSE BY 1/4 TURN AND 2 OUNCES OF LIQUID HAD LEAKED OUT ONTO THE OUTER CARTON. THE OUTER CARTON WAS A DOUBLE WALLED FIPERBOARD BOX AND THERE WAS NO INNER PACKAGING.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010565</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 15:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024010440</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024010440&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-26T15:11:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KANSAS CITY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: R&amp;L CARRIERS SHARED SERVICES, L.L.C.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On January 18, 2024, one (1) 55-gallon drum of UN1993 was punctured by a skid and released approximately less than one (&amp;lt;1) gallon of product to the top of the drum and cardboard underneath. R+L Carriers retained Cura Emergency Services, LC who dispatched a crew from Environmental Works, Inc. to remediate the impacted site.  EWI personnel utilized a chemical pump to transfer the contents of the damaged 55-gallon drum into a new 55-gallon drum. Crews then utilized one (1) 95-gallon open top drum to overpack and contain the damaged 55-gallon drum. EWI personnel collected the damaged cardboard for disposal. Crews staged the new drum onsite to be handled by R+L personnel. R+L personnel took possession of the waste to be added to the facility waste stream.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024010440</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 15:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010597</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010597&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-26T15:11:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-20&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EARTH CITY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: FULLY LABELED HAZ-MAT SHIPMENT WAS VISUALLY DISCOVERED WET IN APPEARANCE BY A SORTER IN PRIMARY SORT AISLE-3. WITHOUT TOUCHING THE PKG HE EVACUATED THE AREA AND NOTIFIED HIS IMMEDIATE SUPERVISOR. DMP WAS CONTACTED AND WITHIN 2 MINUTES A DESIGNATED RESPONDER ARRIVED, DONNING THE PROPER PPE AND WITH A FULLY STOCKED SPILL CART. AFTER FOLLOWING THE DECISION TREE   APPROPRIATE RESPONSE SHEET THE DAMAGE WAS CONTAINED (NO SPILLAGE OUTSIDE OF CARTON), THEN TRANSPORTED TO THE DMP PROCESSING AREA. CLOSER INSPECTION REVEALED THAT THE CAP ON 1 OF 1 POLY 1-GALLON JUGS WAS LOOSE BY A FULL ROTATION, CAUSING APPROX. 6 OUNCES OF THE LIQUID TO SPILL THROUGH THE BREACH AND INTO THE CARTON. THERE WAS NO INTERNAL PACKING MATERIAL AND THE OUTER CARTON WAS A SINGLEWALL FIBERBOARD BOX, RATED AT A 44 LBS/IN EDGE CRUSH TEST (ECT).&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010597</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 15:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024010417</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024010417&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-25T15:11:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-17&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KANSAS CITY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: R&amp;L CARRIERS SHARED SERVICES, L.L.C.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: One 5 gallon metal pail arrived crushed in transit, released 5 gallons in trailer.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024010417</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010392</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010392&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-23T15:11:55+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EARTH CITY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: PACKAGES WERE INSPECTED DUE TO AN ODD SENSE OF GRAVITY, WHITE LABEL AFFIXED STATING RANGE MATERIALS, AND AN ORANGE STICKER SIGNIFYING EXHIBIT MATERIAL C/O WINCHESTER AMMO. UPON INSPECTION OF THE CONTENTS DISCOVERED EACH BOX CONTAINED SMALL ARMS AMMUNITION PACKAGED IN TWO INNER UN SPECIFICATION BOXES. THE INNER BOXES WERE MARKED AS UN0012 CARTRIDGES, SMALL ARMS, 1.4S, AND LTD QTY. THERE ARE NO DANGEROUS GOODS MARKS OR LABELS ON THE OUTERMOST BOXES. ADDITIONAL TRACKING NUMBERS TO THE SAME CONSIGNEE IN NEVADA ARE 1Z4600AW1368783483, 1Z4600AW1367065046, 1Z4600AW1368701829, 1Z4600AW1367878098, 1Z4600AW1368854870, 1Z4600AW1369169216 AND 1Z4600AW1367602607. THESE PACKAGES WERE SHIPPED USING UPS ACCOUNT NUMBER 4600AW, OLIN CORP WINCHESTER - REPCO, 600 POWDER MILL RD., EAST ALTON IL 62024-1273.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010392</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010490</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010490&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-23T15:11:55+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EARTH CITY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: FULLY LABELED HAZ-MAT SHIPMENT WAS VISUALLY DISCOVERED WET IN APPEARANCE BY THE HCD PICK-OFF ON THE PD-4. WITHOUT TOUCHING THE PKG HE TURNED OFF   SECURED THE BELT, EVACUATED THE AREA AND NOTIFIED HIS IMMEDIATE SUPERVISOR. DMP WAS CONTACTED AND WITHIN 4 MINUTES A DESIGNATED RESPONDER ARRIVED DONNING THE PROPER PPE AND WITH A FULLY STOCKED SPILL CART. AFTER FOLLOWING THE DECISION TREE   APPROPRIATE RESPONSE SHEET THE DAMAGE WAS CONTAINED (NO SPILLAGE OUTSIDE OF CARTON), THEN TRANSPORTED TO THE DMP PROCESSING AREA. CLOSER INSPECTION REVEALED THAT THE CAP ON 1 OF 6 POLY 2-LITER DISPENSER/CONTAINERS WAS SLIGHTLY AJAR, CAUSING APPROX. 12 OUNCES OF THE LIQUID TO LEAK THROUGH THE BREACH AND INTO THE CARTON. THERE WAS NO INTERNAL PACKING MATERIAL AND THE OUTER CARTON WAS A SINGLEWALL FIBERBOARD BOX, RATED AT A 275 LBS/IN BURSTING TEST.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010490</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
