<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for LA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for LA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:11:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024031173</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024031173&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-29T18:14:08+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: COVINGTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: hydrochloric acid, bottle found inside an open box DescribePack: loose cap, exterior contents of box was ripped open DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Placed inside hazmat tote with lid&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024031173</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 18:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024030557</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024030557&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-29T18:14:08+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-15&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SCOTT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDEX FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Associate did not block and/or brace freight properly for transport.  Freight was crushed causing release of product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024030557</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 18:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024030519</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024030519&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-28T15:13:06+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BASTROP&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: OCCIDENTAL CHEMICAL CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: At approximately 8:30 am, a OxyChem truck driver was delivering Caustic Soda to a customer site (Morehouse BioEnergy) located in Bastrop, LA. The driver met with the customer site operator, completed the “In the Interest of Safety Form” (which is a form utilized by OxyChem truck drivers to ensure that enough space exists in a customer tank prior to unloading), hooked up offloading hoses, and began offloading. Near the end of the offloading process, product began to overflow from the customer&amp;#x27;s storage tank into the containment area. The OxyChem truck driver immediately shut down the offloading process. The customer site operator was present with the driver when the overflow occurred and made a comment that they would have to check the tank level indicator for accuracy because the calculation during the completion of the “In the Interest of Safety Form” showed that there was sufficient capacity available within the storage tank. Customer site personnel washed down the area. The spill was estimated to be approximately 75-gallons. No injuries, property damage, or environmental impact as a result of the incident.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024030519</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 15:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024030551</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024030551&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-27T15:12:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BATON ROUGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ILLINOIS CENTRAL RAILROAD COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 18000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 03-05-2024 a CN transportation employee observed liquid running down the side of tank car from the top # UTLX 668009 at the CN Baton Rouge Yard located in Baton Rouge, LA. The employee reported the observation to the Transportation Manager who in turn initiated an emergency response from the CN Dangerous Goods Team. The on duty Dangerous Goods Officer dispatched an emergency response contractor to the yard to investigate. The responding contractor&amp;#x27;s initial observation found product residue on both sides of the tank car. Further assessment revealed that all (6) manway cover swing bolts were less than tool tight (could turn by hand) with (1) of the swing bolts in the down position causing a leak from the manway cover due to an improper seal of the gasket. The shipper security seal was found to be intact. The shipper manway cover security seal was removed and the cover was opened for the purpose of replacing the gasket. The manway cover swing bolts were then tightened in a star pattern utilizing an 18&amp;quot; pipe wrench. The tank car was then moved to an accessible track for the purpose of exterior cleaning.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024030551</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024030550</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024030550&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-27T15:12:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-02-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: GEISMAR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ILLINOIS CENTRAL RAILROAD COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 21000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 02-24-2024 a CN transportation employee observed liquid dripping down the side of tank car # UTLX 125078 (Loaded - Spent Sulfuric Acid - UN ID - 1832 - Class 8) while performing switching operations at the CN Geismar Yard located in Geismar, LA. The employee notified the CN Transportation Manager who in turn notified the CN Dangerous Goods Team for an emergency response. The responding CN Dangerous Goods Officer performed an inspection of the tank car and noted spillage on the BL side of the car and liquid dripping the eduction line securement flange. Further inspection revealed: (1) of the (4) flange securement fasteners was not properly tightened and could be freely moved by hand. The 1&amp;quot; air valve was in the completely open position with its securement plug securely installed. The 2&amp;quot; liquid eduction line securement cap was less than tool tight (could be turned by hand. The loose liquid eduction line cap was the source of the leak. The tank car&amp;#x27;s internal pressure was relieved through the 1&amp;quot; air valve stopping the leak. The Liquid eduction line securement cap was properly tightened with an 18&amp;quot; pipe wrench. The 1&amp;quot; air valve was closed, and its securement plug was properly tightened with an 18&amp;quot; pipe wrench. The tank car was then decontaminated by a CN hired contractor. A contractor hired by the responsible party replaced all (4) liquid eduction line flange bolts and securement nuts. The tank car was then pressured up to 10 PSI with a standard air compressor and inspected for leaks. No leaks were discovered.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024030550</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024020039</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024020039&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-03-27T15:12:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-23&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Bossier city&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SOUTHEASTERN FREIGHT LINES INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 2&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: At 03:38 pallet was pulled off trailer a drip was noticed, it was loaded back in the trailer. leak was contained to our trailer and the dock. It was noticed that the pallet seemed to be wedged under a load bar damaging a box of pool supplies. At 5:00 the odor was getting worse it was believed the amount Ieaking was more than first thought, hazmat one was called at 05:08 to come and clean up the material. Hazmat one arrived at 06:45 and completed at 11:02.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024020039</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
