<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for AR</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for AR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:12:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2023070674</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2188904&gt;E-2023070674&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2188904&gt;E-2023070674&lt;/A"&gt;Report E-2023070674&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-08-08T15:12:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-07-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Benton&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: HERITAGE TRANSPORT, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: During off loading, technicians at the receiving facility observed a cubic yard fiberboard container of hazardous debris was smoldering. The debris was contaminated with acetone and methyl ethyl ketone. The technicians isolated the container to an area of the receiving pad and extinguished with an ABC extinguisher. The contents were repacked to a new container and dry ice was added. The repackaged material was scanned with an RFID camera and determined not to have an elevated temperature.  While unloading the remaining containers of debris, technicians found that a drum of methyl methacrylate had partially released some of its contents. The material solidified as expanded foam. The solidified material was repackaged and sampled for analysis. All containers on the trailer were imaged with RFID camera and found to not exhibit elevated temperatures.   No materials were released.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2023070674</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2023070631</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2188804&gt;E-2023070631&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2188804&gt;E-2023070631&lt;/A"&gt;Report E-2023070631&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-08-08T15:12:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-06-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CARLISLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On June 19, 2023, at 0722 ET, an XPO Logistics tractor trailer (truck # 5322228, trailer #321-6811) was involved in a rollover accident when traveling down Interstate 40 eastbound. As a result of the accident, non-regulated “FM-9058 IBCQ” and UN1263 “Thermo Sorb VOC” released impacting the asphalt and soil shoulder as well as into the ditch. No storm drains or waterways were impacted by the release. At 1120 ET, XPO Logistics retained Emergency Response and Training Solutions (ERTS) to manage and oversee the above referenced incident. ARTG Environmental was secured to perform all onsite cleanup and remediation activities. At 1315 ET, ARTG personnel arrived onsite to conduct an initial site assessment. Billy’s Wrecker service was also onsite and towed the damaged unit along with the damaged cargo to their yard. ARTG secured the impacted soil and roadside area with boom and departed site to head to the wrecker yard. Once the contractors arrived at the wrecker yard, poly sheeting was utilized to secure the damaged trailer while awaiting the arrival of a relief trailer. The crew departed site for the day.  On June 20 and 21, 2023, ARTG personnel returned to the spill site to complete the excavation. The crew advised the product released had traveled down and embankment in 10” tall grass but did not reach a nearby creek which was approximately 15’ away. The crew dug approximately 1’ deep into the ditch due to woodchip material being in the ditch, allowing for a more porous surface. The impacted shoulder measured approximately 250&amp;#x27; x 4&amp;#x27; leading into a slope measuring approximately 60&amp;#x27; x 30&amp;#x27; which led into the ditch in an 80&amp;#x27; x 6&amp;#x27; area. A total of approximately 270-tons of impacted soil was excavated and staged roadside, secured with poly sheeting awaiting disposal.   On June 23, 2023, ARTG returned to the tow yard to complete the trailer cleanout. All unimpacted freight was offloaded into a relief trailer. The contractors were able to confirm during this cleanup what material was released to the roadside. Approximately 500-gallons of non-regulated FM-9058 released from (2) 275-gallon poly totes as well as approximately 40-gallons of UN1263 “Thermo-Sorb VOC” released from (8) 5-gallon metal pails. The damaged pails of paint were containerized into (2) 55-gallon metal drums which were transported to the XPO terminal located 6101 Lindsey Rd, Little Rock, AR 72206, for terminal personnel to manage. The two totes are staged at ARTG’s shop pending disposal.  On July 11, 2023, ARTG returned to the site to take confirmation samples for site closure, lab results are still pending.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2023070631</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2023070669</title>
      <link>https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2189464&gt;X-2023070669&lt;/A</link>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="https://portal.phmsa.dot.gov/PDFGenerator/getPublicReport/OHMIR_5800-1?INCIDENTID=2189464&gt;X-2023070669&lt;/A"&gt;Report X-2023070669&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-08-05T21:09:27+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-06-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LOWELL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: PACKAGE WAS SCANNED AS A CODE 10 INSPECTION BY THE DRIVER AT 12:36PM. upon inspection the inner aluminum were dented at the bottom. This indicates the package was dropped. Package was taken back to the terminal for inspection and placed in a hazmat bag and box. DescribePack: Unable to find the place on the 2 cans that are leaking. It appears they were dropped causing a hairline crack. the movement of the van caused the liquid to slightly leak onto the other cans and cause the outer box to be damp. DurationRel: 3 and MitigateEffect: Placed in hazmat drum and bag.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2023070669</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 21:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
