<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for ME</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for ME</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:19:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024061094</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024061094&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-06-28T18:14:46+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-06-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LEWISTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ME&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: The package was discovered wet upon opening the trailer at the beginning of the pre-load sort at around 2:30am according to the OPS Supervisors on duty.  Package was then placed into red line hazmat bin &amp;amp; brought to QA for inspection.  When the package was discovered by QA, the box was soaked/stained on one side &amp;amp; ripped open.  The fiberboard box also had several class 8 corrosive markings, UN/USA markings, &amp;amp; hazmat shipping paperwork attached to it.  4 bottles of Nu-Brite Condenser Coil Cleaner were found inside the box w/ 2 each separated by a fiberboard liner.  2 of the bottle&amp;#x27;s caps had been crushed/bent downward into the body &amp;amp; the 3rd was crushed/bent/squeezed on its body in the middle on each side, causing the contents to leak through the caps.  3 of the bottles were dented on several areas as well.  During the inspection process an additional red line hazmat bin was used to inspect the box &amp;amp; contents.  A long green rubber glove &amp;amp; several biodegradable single use nitrile gloves were used to handle the corrosive substance.  The Improper Shipping Form &amp;amp; Damaged Package Report were filled out &amp;amp; all of the Contents, fiberboard box, &amp;amp; PPE were placed into a lined salvage drum.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024061094</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
