<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for WY</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for WY</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 09:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024020365</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024020365&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-26T15:11:07+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ELK MOUNTAIN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AIRGAS SPECIALTY PRODUCTS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: The accident is still under investigation to determine the cause.  What we know is the vehicle veered to the right leaving the interstate and rolling multiple times.  Due to the rollover, a 2 inch pipe on the back end of the tank was broken off causing the loss of ammonia.  Carbon Count FD, WY State Police and EMT&amp;#x27;s responded to the scene.  I80 was closed for an estimated 5 hours, favorable wind direction allowed the interstate to reopen.  We dispatched our local plant manager to the scene to help determine the severity of the leak.  Once we received information back, it was determined to tarp and cover the release to help contain the fugitive vapors near the truck.  Our Field Service team was activated and sent to the site to remove the remaining liquid ammonia from the truck to allow for a safe recovery of the vehicle by the tow company.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024020365</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 15:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024020357</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024020357&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-02-21T15:11:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LITTLE AMERICA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: US Xpress, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: It was reported that approximately 10-15 gallons of battery acid released due to battery housing fault. The release impacted a 6’ X 2’ area on the asphalt underneath the trailer and trailer floor. No storm drains or waterways were reported to be impacted by the release. EnviroServe arrived on-site and neutralized the acid with a caustic material then deployed absorbents to solidify the release. The contractor collected and containerized the impacted batteries into 3-95-gallon poly drums and all clean-up debris into 1-55-gallon poly drums. The damaged batteries that were overpacked into 3–95-gallon poly DFs were secured inside the trailer for transit. EnviroServe departed the site with the 1–55-gallon poly drum and staged the waste at their office pending disposal.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024020357</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 15:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
