<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for AK</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for AK</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024110328</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024110328&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-19T12:23:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-15&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Anchorage&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: LYNDEN AIR CARGO, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Aircraft landed at Ralph Wien Memorial Airport in Kotzebue Alaska. After the offload, the Loadmaster walked the freight slated for upload. Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s ground handler FBX handles multiple different air carriers, and consolidated freight from three different customers. In which two of the customers freight was slated for another air carrier mixed in with the scheduled freight for Lynden Air Cargo. The Loadmaster failed to recognize the additional cargo and therefore did not notice the additional hazardous materials. The consolidated cargo was then loaded and then flown back to Ted Stevens Anchorage Airport to Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s facility. On September 18th Lynden Air Cargo was getting the shipment ready to be transported over the road to the one customer that was the only shipper we were aware of. During that phase the extra hazmat and pieces were identified, and an internal investigation ensued.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024110328</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024110325</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024110325&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-19T12:23:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-15&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Anchorage&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: LYNDEN AIR CARGO, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 1. E-2024110325 Aircraft landed at Ralph Wien Memorial Airport in Kotzebue Alaska. After the offload, the Loadmaster walked the freight slated for upload. Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s ground handler FBX handles multiple different air carriers, and consolidated freight from three different customers. In which two of the customers freight was slated for another air carrier mixed in with the scheduled freight for Lynden Air Cargo. The Loadmaster failed to recognize the additional cargo and therefore did not notice the additional hazardous materials. The consolidated cargo was then loaded and then flown back to Ted Stevens Anchorage Airport to Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s facility. On September 18th Lynden Air Cargo was getting the shipment ready to be transported over the road to the one customer that was the only shipper we were aware of. During that phase the extra hazmat and pieces were identified, and an internal investigation ensued.   2. E-2024110326 Actual PSN is Engine, Internal Combustion, Flammable Liquid Powered Class 3 Aircraft landed at Ralph Wien Memorial Airport in Kotzebue Alaska. After the offload, the Loadmaster walked the freight slated for upload. Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s ground handler FBX handles multiple different air carriers, and consolidated freight from three different customers. In which two of the customers freight was slated for another air carrier mixed in with the scheduled freight for Lynden Air Cargo. The Loadmaster failed to recognize the additional cargo and therefore did not notice the additional hazardous materials. The consolidated cargo was then loaded and then flown back to Ted Stevens Anchorage Airport to Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s facility. On September 18th Lynden Air Cargo was getting the shipment ready to be transported over the road to the one customer that was the only shipper we were aware of. During that phase the extra hazmat and pieces were identified, and an internal investigation ensued.   3. E-2024110327 Aircraft landed at Ralph Wien Memorial Airport in Kotzebue Alaska. After the offload, the Loadmaster walked the freight slated for upload. Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s ground handler FBX handles multiple different air carriers, and consolidated freight from three different customers. In which two of the customers freight was slated for another air carrier mixed in with the scheduled freight for Lynden Air Cargo. The Loadmaster failed to recognize the additional cargo and therefore did not notice the additional hazardous materials. The consolidated cargo was then loaded and then flown back to Ted Stevens Anchorage Airport to Lynden Air Cargo&amp;#x27;s facility. On September 18th Lynden Air Cargo was getting the shipment ready to be transported over the road to the one customer that was the only shipper we were aware of. During that phase the extra hazmat and pieces were identified, and an internal investigation ensued.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024110325</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024110485</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024110485&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-19T12:23:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANCH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ALASKA AIRLINES&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: While screening shipment through x ray, found item that looked like an aerosol can. Performed physical search and found 1 aerosol can of repel.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024110485</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024110488</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024110488&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-19T12:23:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANCH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ALASKA AIRLINES&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee. would have been on passenger aircraft.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024110488</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024110489</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024110489&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-19T12:23:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-10&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANCH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: Undeclared Shipment with no Release&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ALASKA AIRLINES&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 1. X-2024110489 Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee. would have been on passenger aircraft.   2. X-2024110490 Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee. would have been on passenger aircraft.  3. X-2024110491 Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee. would have been on passenger aircraft.  4. X-2024110492 Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee. would have been on passenger aircraft.  5. X-2024110493 Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee, and would have been on a passenger aircraft.  6. X-2024110494 Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee. would have been on passenger aircraft.  7. X-2024110495 Customer dropped off a bunch of freight at Cargo back door. Ramp agent brought me the slip with the weight and dimensions. Shipment was booked. We started the physical search process as the customer stated their shipment was Household goods and Tools. During the process my team found multiple Dangerous Good items in separate boxes and totes. Shipment booked to Milwaukee. would have been on pass&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024110489</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
