<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for NM</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for NM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 09:16:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024060307</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024060307&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-06-18T15:12:21+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-06-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ALBUQUERQUE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: attachment Name:haz 4.JPG&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024060307</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 15:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024060250</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024060250&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-06-18T15:12:21+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-06-03&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Albuquerque&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SAIA MOTOR FREIGHT LINE, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Damaged during pick up and delivery&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024060250</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 15:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024060127</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024060127&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-06-14T15:12:47+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ALBUQUERQUE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 5000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: approximately .5 gallons of UN 2290 Isophorone Diisocyanate was released from (1) 55-gallon due to unknown causes - there appears to be a pinhole. No drains, soils, or waterways were reported impacted.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024060127</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024051203</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024051203&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-06-12T15:12:18+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-26&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Manuelito&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: BNSF RAILWAY COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 235000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: X-2024051203: H-BELPHX1-25A derailed containing six Propane cars that were involved in fire due to container breaches/damage. NATX 400688 suffered jacket damage and some dents. The car suffered a 19&amp;quot;x2&amp;quot; heat-induced tear on the &amp;quot;B-end&amp;quot;. This car was turned over in a pit and burned itself out after consuming all remaining propane liquid.  X-2024051204: H-BELPHX1-25A derailed containing six Propane cars that were involved in fire due to container breaches/damage. UTLX 952565 suffered jacket damage and some dents. After being exposed to flame impingement for hours, the tank suffered what appears to be a heat-induced tear measuring about 6&amp;quot;x1&amp;quot; on the top of the tank, underneath the jacket. The tank also had a significant blister at this point as well. Significant heat damage to protective housing as well. This car was turned over in a pit and burned itself out after consuming all remaining propane liquid.  X-2024051207: H-BELPHX1-25A derailed containing six Propane cars that were involved in fire due to container breaches/damage. UTLX 955642 suffered jacket damage and some dents. The tank suffered a puncture/tear toward the A-end of the car measuring about 2&amp;#x27;x3&amp;#x27;. This car was turned over in a pit and burned itself out after consuming all remaining propane liquid.  X-2024051208: H-BELPHX1-25A derailed containing six Propane cars that were involved in fire due to container breaches/damage. UTLX 954193 suffered jacket damage and some dents on each end, but no container failure. After being exposed to flame impingement for hours, all gaskets/o-rings were burnt out from valves under the protective housing and product burned from these orifices. The protective housing also had significant damage. This car had burned itself out after consuming all remaining propane liquid.  X-2024051209: H-BELPHX1-25A derailed containing six Propane cars that were involved in fire due to container breaches/damage. UTLX 959911 suffered jacket damage and some dents including a significant B-end head dent, but no container failure. After being exposed to flame impingement for hours, all gaskets/o-rings were burnt out from valves under the protective housing and product burned from these orifices. This car was turned over in a pit and burned itself out after consuming all remaining propane liquid.  X-2024051210: H-BELPHX1-25A derailed containing six Propane cars that were involved in fire due to container breaches/damage. UTLX 953969 suffered jacket damage and some dents including a dent on each end, but no container failure. This car did have multiple PRD venting cycles due to being exposed to heat/fire for hours. This car was liquid flared and then vapor flared to remove all remaining product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024051203</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
