<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for ID</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for ID</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 21:11:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024050624</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024050624&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-05-17T21:11:01+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BOISE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ID&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ABF FREIGHT SYSTEM, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Doug Olsen Road Driver stated that he noticed a leak from trailer 89562 when he stopped to use the restroom at a truck stop. Doug stated that there was a smell coming from the trailer but did not see any leak. Doug was advised by safety anytime there is a smell or a spill, Safety is to to called imm ediately Doug stated he called his dispatch to direct him to SC 143 to have the smell coming from the trailer looked at. Doug stated when he arrived at SC143 he saw where something started to leak out of the trailer on to the ground. Doug stated it looked to be 10oz on the payment of the parking lot  and some on the rear bumper of the trailer. Doug opened the trailer doors up and stated the smell was so strong that he had to walk away from the trailer to clean air. Doug stated he does think it is a Hazmat on the trail that is leaking do to the smell coming from the trailer. CURA was called to a ssist with the spill.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024050624</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 21:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
