<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for WV</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for WV</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040656</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040656&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-16T18:13:46+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CHARLESTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WV&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 1. X-2024040656 SequenceEvent: The Hazmat was loaded on a van and before dispatch the driver informed the package of the leak. The package handler immediately notified QA given the close proximity to the QA cage. QA notified management and responded to the spill. The damage packages were removed and placed in lined hazmat totes. The leak was contained and the spilled liquid was neutralized. DescribePack: Loose caps. Bottles are in a spill containment bag(failed) used by the shipper so it is unsafe to do an inspection without the risk of spilling the amount still left in the bag. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Absorbent pads and neutralizer was used on the spilled liquid. The leaking hazmat was placed inside a line hazmat tote.   2. X-2024040657 SequenceEvent: The Hazmat was loaded on a van and before dispatch the driver informed the package of the leak. The package handler immediately notified QA given the close proximity to the QA cage. QA notified management and responded to the spill. The damage packages were removed and placed in lined hazmat totes. The leak was contained and the spilled liquid was neutralized. DescribePack: Loose caps. Bottles are in a spill containment bag(failed) used by the shipper so it is unsafe to do an inspection without the risk of spilling the amount still left in the bag. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Absorbent pads and neutralizer was used on the spilled liquid. The leaking hazmat was placed inside a line hazmat tote.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040656</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024040351</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024040351&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-16T18:13:46+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-29&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CHARLESTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WV&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: The hazmat was loaded into the belly of a trailer and was placed on its side ignoring the orientation arrows. Package handler had discovered it and noticed that it was wet and notified management. QA responded to, contained, and neutralized the spill. The hazmat was contained in a lined hazmat tote. DescribePack: The cap had a slow leak when placed on its side. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: The spilled liquid was neutralized and the package was place into a lined hazmat tote by QA.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024040351</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024040123</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024040123&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-10T15:11:54+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BELLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WV&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: It was reporedt a one gallon release of regulated UN1993 &amp;quot;SG-500B&amp;quot; arrived damaged at Terminal XCA. The caller stated that (1) a 330-gallon IBC tote released the material as a result of a open valve impacted Trailer #315-7238. The caller advised that the valve was secured prior to calling the spill in. The SDS was reviewed with the terminal who felt comfortable completing the clean-up with terminal-issued PPE. (1) 5-gallon metal drum containing the impacted &amp;quot;Oil Dri&amp;quot; absorbent material, and issued PPE were containerized and left as waste onsite for the terminal to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024040123</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 15:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
