<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for FL</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for FL</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 06:29:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030196</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030196&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-04-20T00:57:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: JACKSONVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: FL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CSX TRANSPORTATION, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 1200&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 3/12/2025, at 12:29 hours, FRA Inspector David Robinson, reported at the CSX Moncrief Yard in Jacksonville, Florida the GATX 205634, a loaded tank car of Flammable Liquid, N.O.S (Turpentine) was leaking from the vapor line valve. The car was isolated and the shipper, International Paper Co, was notified via CHEMTREC (Report #2025031200135). Hulls Environmental, a CSXT response contractor, was dispatched to the scene and found the vapor line valve partially open and secondary closure plug less than tool tight. Contractor personnel closed the vapor line valve and properly tool tighten the secondary closure plug. Contractor personnel also corrected 1 of 6 manway swing bolts less than tool tight that was identified by the FRA inspector.  The issue identified and corrective actions were communicated to the shipper’s representative- Marceia Cox (901-229-4591).&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030196</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 00:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
