<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MN</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MN</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:35:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024010268</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024010268&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-18T15:13:34+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROSEVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDEX FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Associate did not block and/or brace freight properly for transport.  Freight was crushed causing release of product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024010268</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024010181</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024010181&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-17T15:11:26+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-01-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: FRIDLEY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: XPO Logistics terminal XMP experienced a UN2874 Airkure 241 EX Resin release from a 275-gallon poly tote. ERTS dispatched contractors to conduct cleanup operations.  Contractors arrived onsite and confirmed approximately 1 pint of material released to a 2’ x 2’ area of the concrete dock floor due to a puncture to the top corner of the tote. The material was transferred from the damaged tote into a new one. The damaged tote was then cut up and containerized. Absorbents were deployed and worked into the impacted area. The cut up tote, impacted absorbents, and PPE were containerized into a 55-gallon metal drum. All waste was staged onsite for terminal personnel to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024010181</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010258</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010258&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-17T15:11:26+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-20&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROGERS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: someone called out a damaged hazmat around door 133 on the load side. HAP specialist responded to the call and brought the package, in a lined tote, back to the damage area. he placed it atop the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. DescribePack: one bottle leaked due to the entire package having been upside down. employees on the load side did not specify whether the package fell off something or a package handler mishandled it somehow, but it is clear that something happened after it was removed from the IC belt on the load side. DurationRel: 0 and MitigateEffect: immediate cleanup performed. placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010258</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010282</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010282&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-17T15:11:26+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SAINT PAUL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Upon unload of trailer into local 551, hazmat was found to be dripping slowly. Pail was put into a hazmat salvage pail in a plastic hazmat bag. DescribePack: Crack on bottom of pail through raised portion. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Amphomag and absorbant used. Package contained in bag.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010282</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010284</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010284&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-17T15:11:26+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-21&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROGERS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: someone noticed that the package was damaged and smelled slightly of alcohol. that person set the package aside, placed it in a lined tote, brought it to the damage area, and moved it to the drain mats. in-house cleanup, awaiting disposition. DescribePack: one bottle leaked due to loose cap. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010284</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024010174</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024010174&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-17T15:11:26+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LAKEVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDEX FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Associate did not block and/or brace freight properly for transport.  Freight was crushed causing release of product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024010174</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2024010286</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2024010286&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-16T18:13:17+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ROGERS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: 1. X-2024010286 SequenceEvent: HAP specialist was going through the unload bank when he spotted the damaged hazmat sitting on the rollers on its side.  the package was leaking a slow dribble onto the floor. He called the HESS specialist to ask for a lined tote and cleanup material to perform immediate in-house cleanup. upon completion, HESS specialist brought the package in a lined tote back to the damage area and moved it to the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. DescribePack: one bottle leaked due to loose cap. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: immediate in-house cleanup. placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats.   2. X-2024010289 SequenceEvent: HAP specialist discovered this damaged hazmat at the same time as the package in Hazmat Incident No.117328, in the unload. He called HESS specialist to bring him a lined tote and cleanup material. HESS specialist did as requested, then took from him the damaged hazmat in its tote and brought this back to the damage area, placing it atop the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. DescribePack: two bottles leaked due to loose caps DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: immediate in-house cleanup performed. placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats.   3. X-2024010300 SequenceEvent: HAP specialist discovered this package in the unload when placing several other damaged hazmats into lined totes for the HESS specialist to bring back to the damage area. As this was in the same MPS as the others and found in the same trailer, HAP specialist elected to have it inspected just in case. HESS specialist placed the package&amp;#x27;s tote atop the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. The following day, HESS specialist inspected the contents and found that one bottle had leaked. DescribePack: one bottle leaked due to loose cap DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats.   4. X-2024010302 SequenceEvent: HAP specialist discovered this package in the unload when placing several other damaged hazmats into lined totes for the HESS specialist to bring back to the damage area. As this was in the same MPS as the others and found in the same trailer, HAP specialist elected to have it inspected just in case. HESS specialist placed the package&amp;#x27;s tote atop the drain mats in the incoming damaged hazmat/LQ area. The following day, HESS specialist inspected the contents and found that one bottle had leaked. DescribePack: one bottle leaked due to loose cap DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: placed in lined tote, moved to drain mats.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2024010286</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 18:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2023121116</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2023121116&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-01-12T18:13:06+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-21&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SOUTH SAINT PAUL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNION PACIFIC RAILROAD COMPANY INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Product was discovered dripping along both side(s)of loaded tank car CPCX 115015. It was found that the (A) End liquid valve was partially open, and the valve closure plug was less than tool tight. The valve was closed and the leaked stopped, tighten the plug and released car for movement.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2023121116</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
