<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for LA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for LA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:37:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2023120349</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2023120349&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-12-30T17:46:52+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SHREVEPORT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: XPO Logistics terminal LSL experienced a UN1993 WCW6400 Combination Product release from a 330-gallon poly tote. ERTS dispatched contractors to complete cleanup and a liquid tote transfer. Contractors arrived onsite and liaised with onsite LSP contact, Jay Hardy. Crew confirmed approximately 1.5-ounces of product released to the tote lid only which was padded up with an absorbent pad. The release was caused by a crack to the top corner of the tote as a result of improper loading. The product was then transferred via pump, at the requested of the LSP, into a new tote for shipment on. The damaged tote was then cut up and containerized along with all impacted absorbent pads and PPE into a 55-gallon poly drum. The waste was staged onsite for terminal personnel to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2023120349</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2023120959</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2023120959&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-12-30T17:46:52+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CARENCRO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Package was found leaking in trailer during unloading process.  Package was immediately taken out of sortation.  Package was taken to QA processing area for processing. DescribePack: Upon inspection discovered One bottle is cracked on side and handle on bottle is broken.  Large crack on side of bottle, most of liquid leaked out into box. DurationRel: 2 and MitigateEffect: Package was immediately taken out of sortation when leak was found. Package was placed inside a blue hazmat bag inside a red hazmat tote and taken to Hazmat area for processing.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2023120959</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2023120973</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2023120973&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-12-30T17:46:52+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SAINT ROSE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Package was returned to the warehouse by the driver with the container completely drained. When discovered package was placed outside of the van into the grass while the degreaser drained from the bottom of package. DescribePack: When package was returned back to the warehouse a small crack was found on the bottom of the package the size of a pea. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: At the time of release the package was placed off the truck onto the grass so other packages wouldn&amp;#x27;t be affected.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2023120973</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2023120990</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2023120990&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2023-12-30T17:46:52+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2023-12-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BATON ROUGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Fedex Ground Package System, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: SequenceEvent: Management notified QA about leaking hazmat in the unload area. Package was removed from trailer; and placed into a red hazardous tote to be moved to the hazmat cage for inspection. DescribePack: After inspecting hazmat, there was a huge wet stain at the top of the box. There was no inner packing inside of the box to keep bottles from damaging. Also bottles had loose caps which caused liquid to leak inside. DurationRel: 1 and MitigateEffect: Certified person was called to move hazmat out of trailer; and place into red hazardous tote to be moved to hazmat cage for inspection. Also proper eye and wear gear were used in the clean up process.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2023120990</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 17:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
