<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for GA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for GA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 12:19:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024080000</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024080000&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-08-09T00:38:24+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-13&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Douglasville&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: GA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Spirit Express LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 193756&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver was traveling approximately 65 MPH westbound on I-20. He was traveling in the far right lane, when he fell asleep at the wheel. He awoke to stopped traffic in front of him without enough time to come to a safe stop. The driver jerked the wheel to the right to avoid contact with the vehicles in front of him and left the road way. He overturned on a side embankment at MM-43. Upon impact of the crash, a weld in the tank ruptured as well as one of the manhole covers on the top of the trailer. The product slowly leaked out of the trailer for approximately 1 hour. Other vehicles in traffic that witnessed the incident dialed 911. The driver contacted his employer, who in turn contacted Marion Environmental who was closer to the scene and could mitigate the release of gasoline quicker and more efficiently than the carrier could themselves. They set up absorbent booms to control the spilled product. The remainder of the product was pumped over into another trailer and safely transported to the original destination.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024080000</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
