<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MO</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MO</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 21:16:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025040119</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025040119&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-05-06T01:06:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-15&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Labadie&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: THE KIESEL CO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 288295&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: The driver exited Hwy MM, turning on Hwy T, the front right steer tire side wall ruptured, sending the truck into a 20&amp;#x27; ditch. The tractor and trailer rolled on its side, slid across 2 more ditches and then the fifth wheel broke and the tractor continued sliding and came to rest in the final ditch.  The 1st compartment of the trailer ruptured and approx 1,475 gallons of diesel fuel was released.  The temperature was below freezing, the ditches were frozen and the red dye diesel stayed in the snow and on top of the ice.  Kiesel sent a cleanup crew and vacuum trucks to empty the remaining contents of the trailer and vacuum up free liquids.  The recovered materials were transported to the Kiesel terminal. Dams were created in the ditches under the oversight of the USEPA and Missouri Department of Natural Resources to prevent spread of contamination. When the snow melted, cleaning of the ditches commenced.  All of the dams except for 1 have been removed and the cleanup is in its final stage.  Contaminated soils have been excavated and transported to Waste Management Milam Landfill. All response operations performed with approval of USEPA.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025040119</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 01:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
