<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for LA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for LA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:51:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010165</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010165&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-17T06:18:47+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: HAHNVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: LA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: OCCIDENTAL CHEMICAL CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On Saturday, January 4, 2025, a Occidental Chemical driver made a delivery of Hydrochloric Acid to the Occidental Chemical plant located in Hahnville, LA. The Occidental Chemical driver was loaded at an IMTT facility located in Geismar, LA. While the unloading process was underway, it was discovered that the bleeder valve on the product transfer line that goes to the product storage tank was left open. This resulted in approximately 2,500 gallons of Hydrochloric acid being released from the product line into the containment area. No injuries or exposure to chemical occurred as a result of this event, as well as no off-site impact or environmental impact. The offloading process was halted, bleeder valve closed, containment area drained to sump for processing, and remainder of offload was completed.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010165</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 06:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
