<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for TN</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for TN</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 12:26:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030167</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030167&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: NASHVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 21500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: XPO-Logistics contacted ERTS regarding a punctured tote containing hazardous product, BONDERITE C-AK ZX-1 ALKALINE CLEANER. A contractor dispatched and observed an estimated 200-gallon release onto the concrete dock floor and parking lot in a 100’x70’ area as a result of a forklift puncture. Oil dry was applied to the released material and a tote transfer was performed for the residual product left inside of the damaged tote. In total, 23 drums of waste were generated from this response that were taken by the contractor and staged at their location for waste management. The customer refused the new tote with the transferred product, so XPO staged the tote in the waste area for waste disposal. No storm-drains, waterways, or soil were involved in this incident.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030167</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
