<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for CA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for CA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:14:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025020243</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025020243&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: San Jose&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AIR PRODUCTS AND CHEMICALS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 253900&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver was traveling about 7 mph while attempting to make a U-turn on a remote road. Tires on passenger side of trailer entered soft shoulder causing trailer to roll. There were no 3rd parties, no injuries, and some damage to barbwire fence and street sign. Crisis Center was notified and activated. Local Vehicle Recovery Teams from Galt and Santa Clara have responded to the scene. Local fire department responded to scene. Corporate Safety and Environmental notified. Our Air Products driver arrived at the scheduled delivery location with a fully loaded Nitrogen trailer when he approached a gate. The driver exited his vehicle and quickly determined he was at the wrong location. Upon returning to his vehicle, he decided to perform a U-Turn on a narrow two-lane road which had an incline. During the maneuvering, the back end of the trailer dug into soft shoulder and mud, the weight of the trailer pushed the tractor which caused the trailer to break away from the 5th wheel and roll against the tractor. The trailer then rolled over onto its side across the roadway. The trailer released liquid Nitrogen due to the PSV line being damaged. During the roll over event, the tractor’s fuel tank was ruptured causing a diesel spill onto the ground. There were no injuries reported, and no other vehicles involved in this incident.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025020243</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
