<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for TX</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for TX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:19:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030256</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030256&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-22T21:13:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DENISON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: RANGER LANDSTAR INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 89350&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On February 19, 2025, at 1938 ET, Emergency Response and Training Solutions (ERTS) was contacted by Landstar Ranger personnel in Denison, Texas regarding the release of Sulfuric Acid 50%. Contractors were dispatched to the site to perform all onsite clean-up activities. Upon arrival, contractors confirmed the release of 775 gallons of Sulfuric Acid 50% (UN2796, 8, II) from (3) 330-gallon plastic totes onto asphalt and an adjacent ditch. The release was reportedly due to a rollover accident, impacting multiple areas of asphalt and soil. No drains or waterways were impacted by the release. The release was neutralized then cleaned with absorbents and the proper PPE. Removal of impacted soil is pending future remediation by contractors. All waste generated from the emergency response portion of addressing this release was containerized in (6) 55-gallon DFs which were taken onsite by contractors pending proper disposal.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030256</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
