<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for OR</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for OR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:13:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024040040</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024040040&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-25T15:11:03+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: GASTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: MCMINNVILLE GAS INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: There was no leaking of propane from the delivery bobtail. Delivery truck approached a semi  w/ trailer turning left from HWY47 onto Matteson road While going North Two Cars were waiting and the driver of delivery truck Two cars were waiting and the driver of delivery truck had the sun in his eyes and was unable to brake quick enough to  time. The front passenger side of the BMW car , this pushed the car into the back of a pickup causing it to flip onto top of the vehicle and hitting the BMW. Meanwhile the delivery driver flipped onto the drivers side, sliding  to a stop when hitting the semi&amp;#x27;s trailer that had been turning onto Matteson Rd. Mcminniville Gas owner and service guy then accessed the delivery truck &amp;amp; found no leaks. They then emptied 1200 gallons  out of the truck and the tow company pulled the truck  upright.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024040040</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
