<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for RI</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for RI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 12:24:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025020053</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025020053&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-13T00:52:39+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Plaquemine&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: RI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: QUALITY CARRIERS INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: After material was unloaded into consignee&amp;#x27;s storage tank and valves closed, driver was disconnecting hose to tank piping when pressure in hose allowed residue in hose to be released. Small amount of material sprayed onto driver PE and went under gloves onto driver&amp;#x27;s hand. Driver removed gloves and went to Emergency Showers to rinse material from PPE and skin., For driver protection and care he was transported to the hospital ER for evaluation and treatment of skin burn. Driver released from ER and sent home for night. Following day Driver evaluated by personal doctor who recommended he needed surgery to remove some damaged tissue and application of healing skin treatments. Driver admitted to hospital for procedures. Supplemental report will be filed with additional information.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025020053</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
