<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for CA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for CA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:19:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024070112</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024070112&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-15T00:55:32+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-06-17&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: RIVERDALE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: EAST PENN LOGISTICS LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 313220&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: An East Penn Manufacturing Co. driver was heading west bound on Kamm Ave approaching Jameson Ave. The other driver was headed northbound on Jameson Ave. approaching Kamm Ave. The other driver disregarded the posted stop sign and came into the path of the East Penn driver. Collision occurred and the East Penn truck rolled on to its side and came to a final stop at the northwest corner of the intersection. This was a T-Bone event. Police came to the scene and requested help for the cleanup. East Penn hired a hazardous waste cleanup contractor to clean up the batteries that were on the ground and take them back to their shop. East Penn then went back to the contractor to pick up the batteries to take them back to East Penn&amp;#x27;s Salt Lake City, UT facility. The batteries were then sent to one of the East Penn&amp;#x27;s tolling smelters for proper disposal of the batteries at a secondary lead smelter for recycle. East Penn also hired a contractor to do the remediation cleanup of the soil and incident area. The clean up was completed and overseen by the Fresno County Enviromental Health.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024070112</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
