<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for PA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for PA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 09:17:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030248</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030248&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-22T21:13:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-20&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: TYRONE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: PA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: M. C. TANK TRANSPORT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 46000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: This is a customer unload. After arriving at the plant, the driver sits in his Tractor while the customer unloads the trailer. After the customer hooked up, they began to offload with a 3&amp;#x27;&amp;#x27; pump. Approximately 1 hour into the unloading cycle, the trailer suffered a vaccum collapse. It was determined that the customer failed to ensure that a ball valve was open on their vapor recovery line. Approximately 2000 gallons of HCL spilled from the bottom of the trailer During the event. All but 100-200 gallons was caught in their containment area. The remaining material left containment and leaked onto a gravel area leading to the unloading area. 1800 gallons inside containment was pumped into totes, and the material that left containment in a gravel area was neutralized and then disposed of by plant personnel. The trailer will be totaled by our insurance company.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030248</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
