<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for CA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for CA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 06:17:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024110016</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024110016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-07T12:22:36+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: El Cajon&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: COASTAL TRANSPORT CO.,. INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 2607950&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: CTMV was stopped at traffic signal on Navaho Road. When the light turned green, the operator began accelerating to make 90 degree left tum onto Fletcher Parkway. The tum is an&amp;quot;off-camber turn&amp;quot; as the outer tum radius surface is lower than the inner tum radius. The driver failed to respond correctly to this surface condition. As the CTMV turned, the liquid cargo surged to the passenger side of the cargo compartments. The sudden weight shift caused the CTMV to roll over to the right. The CTMV rotated 180 degrees clockwise and came to rest upside down straddling the roadway and sidewalk. Fuel began Ieaking through the venting devices mounted between the rollover rails on the top of the semi-trailer. The fuel flowed downhill along the sidewalk and curb. Fuel entered two storm drain entry points before the entry points were closed by sand bagging. The storm drain was dry down stream. While upside down, the compartments were tapped, and approximately 400 gallons were recovered from the compartments. Fuel recovery and remediation steps were begun immediately. Approximately 1500 gallons were recovered from a concrete utility pit located within the sidewalk underneath the upside down CTMV. The remaining fuel is being recovered by cleaning the storm drain conduit and replacing soil that has absorbed fuel downstream from the spill site. Asphalt roadway surface is being replaced for approximately 200 feet downhill from the spill site. The fuel did not enter any waterway.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024110016</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 12:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024100731</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024100731&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-04T12:23:29+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-26&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Vernon&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SAIA MOTOR FREIGHT LINE, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 15000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Other fell&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024100731</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
