<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MI</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:23:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010291</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010291&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-17&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: RIVERVIEW&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: VEOLIA ES TECHNICAL SOLUTIONS, L.L.C.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On January 17th, 2025, at 12:34, a three-person Veolia team was conducting operations at the ASH Stevens customer site. The Veolia employees were in the process of loading totes onto a box truck using an electric pallet jack. The Veolia box truck was positioned at the customer&amp;#x27;s loading dock.  During the loading procedure, an incident occurred when a tote situated near the front of the box truck (one of the first to be loaded) was accidentally punctured. This happened as the pallet jack operator was attempting to place a second tote behind it, towards the rear/open end of the truck.  The puncture occurred in the left-hand lower quadrant of the 275-gallon tote. As a result, the contents began to leak, flowing from the front of the box truck towards the rear while it was still in the loading dock. The leaking material spilled off the truck and into the customer&amp;#x27;s secondary containment system, where it was successfully contained.  The customer&amp;#x27;s team promptly responded to the situation by transferring the remaining contents of the damaged tote into a new, undamaged container. They also managed to recover the spilled material from the secondary containment area. It is estimated that less than 250 gallons of the material was lost to the customer&amp;#x27;s containment system.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010291</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
