<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for FL</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for FL</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:27:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025070388</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025070388&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-07-23T00:58:10+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-06-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: GAINESVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: FL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: TRANSPORTATION SERVICES UNLIMITED, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 16282&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Transportation Services Unlimited Inc. (TSU) CMV operator arrived at 03:25am to deliver hypochlorite solutions to customer Pinch A Penny 33&amp;#x27;s, owned and operated by Kristine and Michael Moureau, two 1800 gallon above ground storage tanks.  This was a routine delivery for the TSU CMV operator, and the TSU CMV operator failed to properly conduct an inspection of the customer&amp;#x27;s equipment prior to unloading.  Due to this failure, the operator was unaware of the recent installation of the new hypochlorite solutions KemKey connector and the disconnection of the old offloading line. The operator connected his cargo tanker unloading hose to the customer&amp;#x27;s old offloading line, which was no longer connected to the above ground storage tank.  CMV operator began the unloading operations, after a few minutes the operator noticed that the above ground storage tank was not increasing in the amount of hypochlorite solutions.  It was at this time, the operator investigated the cause and found that the unloading operation through the old offloading line was releasing hypochlorite solutions directly to the ground instead of filling the customer&amp;#x27;s tank. The operator immediately terminated unloading operations, thus mitigating any further potential spillage. There was no equipment failure.  The hazardous material release was due to the following:  1) the lack of communication to the CMV operator regarding the installation of the new KemKey connector, 2) the failure to remove/render inoperable the old offloading line, and 3) the CMV operator&amp;#x27;s failure to properly conduct an equipment inspection prior to beginning the unloading process which resulted in the hazardous material release. CBI was contacted to handle the cleanup. https://www.cliffberryinc.com  **** Property owner notified of the hazardous material discharge, and provided a phone number to the National Response Center (NRC). Property owner was notifying the NRC, and the incident/call number was provided to the property owner (not us, so the NRC incident/call number is unknown).****&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025070388</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025060385</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025060385&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-07-23T00:58:10+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-06-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Marianna&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: FL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SEABOARD MARINE, LTD., INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 50000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Truck Driver 1169 reported container GESU672757-9 leaking after driver had stopped at a TA Travel Center (2112 FL-71, Mariana, FL 32448) to fuel. The container was confirmed to be carrying 18 IBC totes of (UN1760, CORROSIVE LIQUID, N.O.S. (AMMONIUM HYDROXIDE, SODIUM HYDROXIDE), CLASS 8, PG II), loaded and sealed by shipper Cytec Industries Technology Solutions at their warehouse, and picked up by driver 1169 earlier that day. Following the initial report, the container was moved to an isolated area of the truck stop, and 911 was contacted. Jackson County police and fire departments responded to the scene; fire department proceeded to cut the seal and enter the container to assess the situation. A.C.T. Environmental was contracted to respond and provide clean-up and disposal services, arriving onsite at approximately 1900 and completing the clean-up at approximately 0600 the following morning (6/19/25). The leak was confirmed to come from one of the IBCs which appeared to have been punctured by a sharp object (potentially a forklift during loading) on one of the sides near the bottom of the IBC.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025060385</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
