<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for TX</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for TX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024040209</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024040209&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-15T15:12:24+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-21&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: AVINGER&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CREEDENCE, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 143782&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: The driver of the vehicle was driving at approximately 60 mph when he felt a drop on the backend of the vehicle.  At that time, the driver lost control of the vehicle and began to fishtail and then the vehicle rolled onto its top. A  witness to the incident informed the driver that he had lost his back passenger wheels off the truck in transit and this caused the loss of control. It was determined that the wheel studs had completely broken off causing this to happen. The wreck and rollover are what caused the damage to the packaging of the chemicals. The duration of the release was approximately 45 minutes. Creedence immediately contacted an emergency response hazmat  clean up crew and got them to the location of the incident. They immediately began containing the spill from spreading and cleaning what had been spilt. Creedence notified the National Response Center of the spill and  TCEQ was on site directing the clean up the following day.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024040209</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024040289</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024040289&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-15T15:12:24+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ORANGE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: RANGER LANDSTAR INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 41500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On March 12, 2024 at 1421 ET, Emergency Response and Training Solutions (ERTS) was contacted by Landstar personnel in Orange, Texas regarding the release of approximately (225) gallons of FERRIC SULFATE SOLUTION, Corrosive Liquid, Acidic, Inorganic, n.o.s. (UN3264, 8, III). Contractors were dispatched to the site to perform all onsite clean-up activities. Upon arrival, contractors investigated and confirmed the release was caused by a load shift due to a hard brake and was contained to the trailer floor and a 100ft x 6ft area of asphalt trailing behind the unit. Contractors neutralized the release then used absorbents and the proper PPE to clean the release. Contractors were able to transfer the remaining product in the damaged tote to a new tote without complication. All waste generated from addressing this release was containerized in (7) 55-gallon DF’s, which was then taken offsite by contractors for proper disposal. **The NRC report has the city of Beaumont (which the spill took place in Orange City), this 5800 report was completed to match the NRC report for fluidity**&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024040289</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
