<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for TN</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for TN</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 01:02:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024110417</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024110417&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-22T12:30:52+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-11-18&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: MEMPHIS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 12000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: XPO Logistics terminal NMP experienced a UN2924 PQ-8 release from a 270-gallon poly tote. ERTS dispatched contractors to conduct cleanup operations. Contractors arrived onsite and confirmed approximately 150-gallons of product released to a 53’ x 8’ area of the trailer floor and an 80’ x 40’ area of the asphalt lot below due to a forklift puncture to the tote. A vac truck was dispatched which transferred the material from the damaged tote into a new one. The vac truck was then utilized to collect all free-standing liquid. Sodium bicarbonate and absorbents were then deployed and worked into the impacted areas to clean and neutralize the impacted areas. One 55-gallon poly drum of recovered liquid product was generated. Crew then generated (10) 55-gallon poly drums of impacted absorbents, boom, PPE, and the empty damaged cut up poly tote. The waste was staged onsite for terminal personnel to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024110417</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 12:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
