<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MD</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MD</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:41:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024060052</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024060052&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-07-20T00:36:44+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-04-25&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: MILLINGTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MD&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: EAST PENN LOGISTICS LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 166135&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: An East Penn Logistics, LLC driver was on Cypress Road Maryland, Rt 291, heading towards the Maryland / Delaware line. While checking in his mirrors he drifted right, went off the road into a ditch and tried to recover back onto the road and over corrected and ended in a roll over onto the driver&amp;#x27;s side. The driver was treated for minor injuries.  The local Police responded to the scene. They called a local towing company to assist in the clean up and the towing of the truck. The Maryland Department of Environment also responded to the call. By the time they arrived, the incident was mostly cleaned up. They were happy with the clean up and no further action to be done via the MD EPA for clean up. The truck and batteries were towed back to Phillips Garage in Sudlersville, MD. The driver returned the next day to help repalletize and package the scrap batteries for shipping back to East Penn Manufacturing, Lyons Station for proper disposal of the batteries at our secondary lead smelter.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024060052</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
