<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for MO</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for MO</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 09:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024060016</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024060016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-06-21T15:17:18+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-06&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Kansas City&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: THE KANSAS CITY SOUTHERN RAILWAY COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 5/6/2024 CPKC Hazmat received notice that a loaded liquid Argon car, MTGX 7050, was observed Ieaking during an inbound train inspection at the Kansas City, MO Knoche yard, and had an iced cabinet. CPKC Hazmat mobilized to the yard along with a railroad qualified response contractor to assist with mitigating the release. Upon arrival, responders found MTGX 7050 to be 85-90% empty. Also, the car needed to be switched into a track where it could be safely secured. Temporary measures were taken to stop the leak utilizing a freeze patch. Hazmat requested the car be isolated in a suitable track for further action. During switching to isolation, the freeze patch failed and after being isolated, the car finished depressurizing. Responders determined the source of the leak was a broken Liquid Sample Valve Feedline(V-13R) in right cabinet, and a loose fitting in the left cabinet on the PB Vapor Recovery Isolation/Check pipe fitting(RCV-1). The total estimated release is 15,336 gallons of liquid Argon(total load loss). The car was on hazmat hold until an OTMA-1 was obtained to move the car to home shop. File Note: Item 19-the quantity released was estimated based on the best information available at the time of filing. This shipment was offered as a&amp;#x27;bulk&amp;#x27; shipment, aka one car load, therefore the exact amount offered in this package is not known to the carrier. This carrier does not have access to mass balance data which can exactly quantify this value.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024060016</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 15:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
