<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for OR</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for OR</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:29:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025060426</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025060426&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-07-23T00:58:10+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-06-19&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Portland&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Don's Mobile Wash&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 5500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Carrier was operating a rented box truck with a GVWR of 25,999 in interstate commerce. Carrier had purchased 26 drums from NW Auto Solutions of reported Hydrofluoric Acid in 55 gallon plastic drums. Carrier reported they did not have shipping papers for the load.   Carrier was travelling NB on I-205 in Portland when they reported they were cut off in traffic, left the highway, and collided with the trailer of a flat-bed trailer which was stopped on the shoulder. The box truck sidewall was penetrated by the flat-bed, resulting in the damage of one of the drums. The entire contents of the drum leaked out onto the highway, resulting in a complete highway closure.   Initial law enforcement responders reported some airway discomfort. One responded was evaluated at a local ER a day after.  Portland Fire Bureau&amp;#x27;s Hazmat response team applied absorbent and mitigated the leak. It is unknown if any of the material leaked into the waterway.   Carrier was hauling without a hazmat endorsed CDL, no placards, no shipping papers, and no emergency response information. USDOT inspection was completed and documented under inspection number ORAL41131179.   Carrier was advised to report to NRC. Reported contacted NRC on 6/21/25 and discovered no report was made. Reporter then made report to NRC.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025060426</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025061636</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025061636&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-07-23T00:58:10+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-06-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ONTARIO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNION PACIFIC RAILROAD COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: GATX 215840 derailed upright, while being re-railed the car was dropped, this resulted in a release from the vapor line due to the plug not being installed and the valve being open.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025061636</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
