<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for PA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for PA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 03:15:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024070201</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024070201&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-07-12T15:12:45+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-07-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: N VERSAILLES&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: PA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Stephen Hudspeth&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On July 8th 2024, at approximately 11:30am, Union Railroad Train 50a was in the process of entering the Port Perry and Dexter Yards with a 96 car loaded iron ore train.  The train was led my four locomotives.  Brakes were applied to the locomotives only and allowed to release on the remainder of the train.  This caused a great deal of force in the train that allowed the cars to leave the track.  Rail dislodged during the derailment impacted the fuel tank of the third from lead locomotive causing it to spill its contents of fuel.  Three of the four locomotives derailed as well as five of the 96 loaded ore cars.  No other material was spilled, the remaining locomotives had no leaks.    Internal responders were notified and responded to the derailment.  The spill response plan was followed alerting the required agencies.  A derailment contractor was called in to re-rail the train, and internal forces were assembled to repair the track.  The liquid product on the ground was collected as quickly as possible into buckets, however most of the product entered the ballast and surrounding soil.  The nearby river was monitored for signs of a sheen, inlets were checked but it was found the fuel had not reached either.  A spill contractor was dispatched to provide lined dumpsters for the contaminated soil.  The contractor also provided a vacuum truck to clean up the track area that could not be reached with an excavator.  Contaminated soil was placed in the lined dumpsters.  Dumpsters are staged for pickup when manifests are created and samples are analyzed.   The area of the spill will be restored with new ballast.  Any recovered fuel will be filtered and re-used elsewhere on the railroad.   The locomotive with the broken fuel tank was checked in the morning and recorded to have about 900 gallons of fuel before the trip.  40 gallons were recovered from the tank before re-railing the locomotive.  The maximum amount spilled would be approximately 860 gallons, however some of that amount was likely used in transit between the start of duty and the derailment.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024070201</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 15:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
