<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for GA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for GA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:13:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024040027</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024040027&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-04-29T15:12:08+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-03-15&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: BRASELTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: GA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: TEAM LOGISTICS COMPANY LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 140000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Team Logistics Driver Eric Bell (Owner Operator 1099 Contractor) was making a bulk delivery of gasoline to Race Trac #232 on 1450 McEver Road, Gainesville, GA 30501. The delivery&amp;#x27;s inception; TransMontaigne Terminal on 3450 Jefferson Road, Athens, GA 30607 loading of Metroplex Energy. In route to the delivery on Highway 53 @ Hoyt Holder Road heading North, in Braselton, GA. Mr. Bell failed to maintain his lane of travel and rolled his tractor trailer. Mr. Bell stated, there were three vehicles in front of him traveling approximately 25 mph, and another vehicle turning right (South) from Hoyt Holder Road causing him to move toward the right shoulder. This movement brought Mr. Bells tires off the road and onto the soft, muddy shoulder. As Mr. Bell brought his tractor back onto the roadway the trailer entered a drop off area that turned the unit over. The tractor trailer rolled completely over with the tractor blocking both sides of Hwy 53, and the trailer positioned upside down arched between the road and the drop off area, slanting down about eight feet. Fortunately, Mr. Bell was able to evacuate the vehicle sustaining no injuries. Once out of the unit, Mr. Bell secured the scene making sure there were no hazardous materials compromising the environment. Jackson County Sheriff&amp;#x27;s Office and Fire Department were dispatched to the scene of the accident. GA DOT also was present to close Highway 53 off and to verify the hazardous cargo was not compromising the environment. GA DOT officer MCO Fortson conducted a DOT inspection on the vehicle following the FMCSA-inspection Platform (Driver/Vehicle Examination Report). Seymour&amp;#x27;s Towing and Recovery responded to the emergency for remediation and recovery. Team Logistics Emergency Team brought another tanker truck to transfer products. After conducting a safety briefing, a plan was put into place. The Jackson County Fire Department evacuated the three residents near the accident location for two hours during the transfer of product for safety, then set up a foam and water deployment location. Seymour&amp;#x27;s grounded and bonded the tanker for transfer, then secured the rolled unit with two wreckers.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024040027</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
