<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for ME</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for ME</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:17:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024050732</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024050732&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-06-03T15:13:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-07&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: WESTBROOK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ME&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: DENNIS K. BURKE INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 40512&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver was delivering gasoline to a gas station.  He brought 4000 gallons divided between multiple pockets of his trailer.  Company policy is to not exceed 90% of a tank&amp;#x27;s capacity, and upon arrival the driver determined the load would be very close to 90%, so he dropped one pocket at a time, sticking the tank before each pocket, and doing the math to ensure each pocket would fit.  Before dropping 1500 gallons from pocket #3, the driver disconnected the delivery hose to stick the tank.  He obtained the inch reading, converted it to gallons, did the required math, and determined the product in the pocket would fit.  He neglected to re-connect the delivery hose before releasing the product.  He realized his mistake immediately, and stopped the flow of product, but in the very short amount of time (just a few seconds, if that) approximately 51 gallons of product was released to the pavement near the fill.     The driver immediately gathered absorbent materials and pads from his spill kit, and did everything he could to contain the release, but product flowed away from the fill, entering a Central Maine Power (CMP) underground electrical vault.  After stopping the release and containing as much as he could, the driver called our company&amp;#x27;s 24/7 Safety line to report the spill.  The on-call Safety Manager immediately called 911 and was connected to Westbrook Fire who responded.  He then called Green Site Services for cleanup, and ME DEP who also responded.   When it was determined some quantity of gasoline had entered the electrical vault, the fire department evacuated the area and shut down the street until CMP was able to respond.  Ultimately all liquid was vacuumed out of the vault, a confined space team entered and pressure washed the vault, and speedy dry was applied to all surface material, and was subsequently removed and disposed of properly.  ME DEP was present for the clean-up as well, and approved.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024050732</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
