<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for TN</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for TN</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 09:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024100114</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024100114&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-05T12:22:11+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-13&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KINGSPORT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SINDLE TRUCKING, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 76044&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: BAE Systems Ordnance Systems Inc. (OSI) is the operating contractor for Holston Army Ammunition  Plant (HSAAP) located at 4509 West Stone Drive in Kingsport, Hawkins County, Tennessee. On  September 13, 2024 a hose rupture during offload of a strong nitric acid tanker resulted in a  release of acid to the environment. A description of the event is outlined below:  The truck driver and operators started the transfer and then moved to observe from a safe location  per standard operating procedure. Approximately 10 minutes after the transfer started, personnel  observed a NOx cloud and nitric acid spray coming from the back of the tanker. After the wind  shifted, the driver made the decision to approach the tanker and activate the emergency stop,  ending the release. Upon further investigation after the incident, personnel found the transfer  hose had failed.  The total amount of nitric acid released from the tanker was 20,988 pounds. It is estimated that  approximately 10,494 pounds of nitric acid drained to the spill basin for the tanker pad and into  the wastewater collection system. Approximately 10,494 pounds sprayed onto the ground next to the  tanker pad. None of the nitric acid traveled to the stormwater channels. Approximately 105 pounds  of NOx was released during the event. A hazmat contractor was promptly hired to clean up the release.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024100114</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
