<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for FL</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for FL</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 15:17:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025060264</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025060264&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-06-22T01:13:25+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-04-25&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: FORT LAUDERDALE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: FL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: JETBLUE AIRWAYS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: CALLER REPORTS (01) LITHIUM BATTERY RELEASED SMOKE INTO THE CABIN OF AN AIRCRAFT. THE SMOKE, POSSIBLY, CAME FROM A POWER BANK, IT IS UNKNOWN WHAT THE EXACT DEVICE WAS AS THE FIRE DEPARTMENT CONFISCATED THE ITEM. THE CAUSE OF THE RELEASE OF SMOKE IS UNKNOWN.   THERE WAS NO DAMAGE TO THE ROW OR SEATS.   THE INCIDENT OCCURRED ON A FLIGHT FROM FORT LAUDERDALE-HOLLYWOOD INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT TO PINDLING INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT IN NASSAU, BAHAMAS approximately 15 minutes prior to landing.  A self-contained cell phone charger went into Thermal runaway and caught fire.  The Crew immediately extinguished the fire and placed the charger in a water bath and secured it in the forward lavatory.  Passengers deplaned normally through the JetBridge and ARFF team took possession of the charger.   FLIGHT NUMBER 1593   1040 IS THE TIME THE INCIDENT OCCURRED IN THE BAHAMAS.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025060264</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 01:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
