<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for ID</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for ID</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 09:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024080122</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024080122&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-10-09T09:22:30+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-08-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: RATHDRUM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ID&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CITYSERVICEVALCON, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 223191&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Truck was traveling north with cruise control set at 61 mph and failed to negotiate a turn. Truck tracked off right side of road onto soft shoulder comprised of sand and gravel. Driver over-corrected and slowed which caused. trailer to jack-knife and overturn onto roadway. Impact of trailer to roadway and abrasion from dragging along road caused two compartments of trailer to be breached. Trailer terminated across both lanes of highway. Trailer sustained damage to rear and center compartments. Rear compartment was damaged due to impact that caused a greater than 12-inch crack along the outer trailer wall and internal vertical wall between rear and center compartment. Center compartment sustained multiple pittings and an approximate 4-inch vertical crack on the side that abraded along roadway (See attached pictures). Absorbent materials consisting of pads, booms and granular matter was dispensed immediately. Emergency response and spill response crews were notified and cleanup activities began immediately by pumping out remaining contents of trailer and removing trailer from roadway along with cleanup of roadway and visible fuel. Soil excavation activities began on August 5, 2024 upon receipt of encroachment permit from Idaho Department of Transportation.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024080122</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
