<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for RI</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for RI</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:31:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025020022</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025020022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-23T00:59:57+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Woodlawn&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: RI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CARPATHIAN WAY INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: I Responded to a single vehicle rollover involving a CMV hauling HAZMAT. The CMV left the roadway, overcorrected, and rolled onto the passenger side. See C10-25-00003 for further details. The jarring from exiting/reentering the roadway, and rolling onto its side, caused the product being shipping to rupture/leak from the trailer. Several Fire Departments responded to the scene, along with MABAS HAZMAT Crew, to contain the spill. Initially, a 100 meter exclusionary zone was established for safety. The crews placed yellow boom in and around the trailer to contain the spill. E-Environmental Solutions was contacted to mitigate the spill. Until deemed safe the estimated duration of release was 2 hours. IBCs appeared to have leaked out of the filler cap due to the overturn- no overt damage observable. Load is intermittently reacting with the atmosphere(emitting gas vapors)- unable to ascertain Ieakage from IBC&amp;#x27;s in nose of trailer. The lane closure will continue until mitigation completed&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025020022</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
