<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for PA</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for PA</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 03:37:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025020052</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025020052&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SHARPSBURG&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: PA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: PENN TANK LINES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 165400&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Truck driver lost control of vehicle, struck cement barrier on side of roadway. Driver over corrected causing the trailer to sway, then rollover. Unit remained on roadway and no other vehicles were involved. This trailer consisted of 4 compartments. The last compartment received a puncture spilling 2,000 gals. of ULSD B2. The product ran down the roadway and entered storm drains that discharged rain fall into Pine Creek. Pine Creek discharges into The Allegheny River approximately 1 /2 mile downstream from the spill. The duration of the release was immediate &amp;amp; flowed freely until fire department was on scene. The trailer was an aluminum MC 306 built by Custom in the year 1995.  Multiple fire departments were on scene along with the PA State Police, Allegheny County Hazmat, Etna Baro Police and others. On initial impact a fire started from product spilled along the barrier wall when contacted and ruptured. The fire department extinguished with no incident. The driver exited from the cab on his own, transported to ER and released with no injuries other than a cut on his hand. The fire departments blocked the drains with booms and other material to stop any continuous flow that could occur. A HM Spill Contractor was called to remove the remaining ULSD from the other 3 compartments. The trailer needed to be drilled to install a pump out hose into the tank. Product was transferred without further incident. The contractor was completing cleanup while the action of pumping the trailer was done. After the truck was righted and removed from the scene under tow, the contractor continued with the cleanup under the supervision of the PennDOT responder. Fire crews installed booms in the creek and at the mouth where the creek empties into the Allegheny River. The creek and river are an ongoing project to retain and remove product. Multiple state and local agencies are involved in monitoring the spill cleanup actions.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025020052</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030151</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030151&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-10&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ALLENTOWN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: PA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 50000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: t 0415 ET, XPO notified ERTS of a cargo release at XAN. It was reported that approximately 100 gallons of Enviroset 40E FNB Resin were released from a 275-gallon plastic tote due to improper loading by XAN. The release impacted trailer #4413259 and the concrete outside the trailer. ERTS will proceed to dispatch a contractor to the site to complete cleanup activities.   Contractors arrived onsite and confirmed approximately 200-gallons of UN2874 Enviroset 40E FNB Resin product released to the entire wooden trailer floor and the concrete beneath the trailer which spread to nine trailer bays, as well as sewer drain was impacted. The contractor applied speedy dry to the release that impacted the concrete and placed booms around the drains as well as the outfall. The estimated 10-gallons still in the tote was solidified with speedy dry and the tote were placed in a roll off for disposal. The contractors flushed the impacted sewer drain and vacuumed and filled (3) totes with impacted water/product. The waste was staged onsite for terminal personnel to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030151</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
