<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for FL</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for FL</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 06:17:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024100689</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024100689&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-05T12:22:11+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-01&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SPRING HILL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: FL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AMERIGAS PROPANE, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 115050&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: S&amp;amp;L Company Transport driver started his workday at 1753 on 9/31/2024. He drove from his parking location at 15222 Hudson Ave., Spring Hill, FL to the Orlando, FL terminal to load his truck. He made two deliveries - the first being in Palmetto, FL at an AmeriGas facility, and the last being in Clearwater a the AmeriGas facility. When Transport Driver completed the final delivery in Clearwater, he drove back to his parking location at 15222 Hudson Ave., Spring Hill, FL, which is an AmeriGas property.   To access this location, the Transport Driver backs in off the roadway to get into the yard. On this morning at 0522, he pulled up headed westbound on Hudson Ave. and began his backing maneuver traveling 3 mph. He was across both lanes of traffic in the middle of his maneuver when a 3rd party vehicle traveling eastbound on Hudson Ave. crashed into the transport trailer. The Transport Driver immediately got out of the vehicle to assess the situation and called 911.   When emergency personnel arrived on scene, the scene was secured and the leak was assessed. There was a small leak coming from the flange of the pump under the transport and emergency personnel and AmeriGas decided it would be best to evacuate the remaining propane in the transport by flaring it off. The responding fire dept. utilized water spray to dissipate some of the propane vapor under the transport before they were able to flare. The leak lasted for roughly 2 hours before flaring equipment could be set up and utilized. The flare was set up and remaining propane was burnt off prior to the transport and 3rd party vehicle being moved and the road re-opened.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024100689</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
