<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for AL</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for AL</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 01:00:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024060113</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024060113&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-08-28T00:45:53+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-13&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CREOLA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: QUALITY CARRIERS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 4&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: UPON ARRIVAL AT CONSIGNEE LOCATION OFFLOADING OPERATIONS STARTED. DUE TO A SLIGHT LEAK AT THE EXTERNAL VALVE CONNECTION CONSIGNEE PERSONEL REJECTED LOAD REQUIRING REPAIR AT OFF-SITE LOCATION. DRIVER PROCEEDED TO REPAIR FACILITY FOR ASSISTANCE. AT EVENT LOCATION, CTMV WAS BROUGHT TO DOORWAY OF REPAIR FACILITY DUE TO WEATHER CONDITIONS. DRIVER ATTEMPTED TO ASSIST MECHANICS BY REMOVING EXTERNAL VALVE FROM HOUSING. ONCE VALVE REMOVED FROM PIPE PRODUCT FLOWED FREELY INTO ENVIROMENT. DRIVER ATTEMPTED TO ACTUATE EMERGENCY SHUTOFF. ACTIVATION OF EMERGENCY SHUTOFF FAILED TO STOP FLOW OF PRODUCT. FACILITY EVACUATED DUE TO PRODUCT RELEASE AND INABILITY TO HAULT FLOW FROM TRAILER. VAPOR CLOUD RESULTED FROM PRODUCT FUMES AND WET WEATHER AT TIME OF INCIDENT. DRIVER SUFFERED CHEMICAL BURNS DURING ATTEMPT TO REMOVE VALVE AND HAULT FLOW, WAS TAKEN TO HOSPITAL. INTERNAL INVESTIGATION UNDERWAY CAUSE OF FAILURE AT THIS POINT APPEARS TO BE INTERNAL VALVE SEATING WHICH PREVENTED PROPER OPERATION OF INTERNAL VALVE SEALING VESSEL.  SUPPLIMENTAL REPORT WILL BE FILED WITH ADDITIONAL DETAILS.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024060113</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
