<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for NJ</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for NJ</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 03:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024080377</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024080377&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-15T00:55:32+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-07-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Clifton&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: BRENNTAG NORTHEAST, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 13250000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: BNE Driver was involved in fatal vehicle accident while traveling east bound on NJ Route 3 (Clifton, NJ), -Lat 40.8673383, Long -74.184025479.  At the time of the accident the EE was driving  BNE tractor #476 and loaded BNE van trailer #159.  After coming in contact with a NJ Transit Bus, the vehicle went off the right side of the roadway, struck the guardrail, and went through a sound barrier wall creating a fire engulfing the tractor, spreading to the trailer, and resulted in fire and two explosions of onboard hazmat (various flammable liquids, and corrosive) freight.  The EE succumbed to their injuries.  Roadway was closed for several hours and Local Clifton Fire Dept was able to extinguish the fire of the vehicle, trailer and freight.  First Call Environmental (ER/Environmental) contractor was able to contain, remediate, and clean-up the affected areas impacted by fire and release of hazmat at direction of EPA and NJDEP.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024080377</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
