<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for TX</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for TX</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:18:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025052185</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025052185&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-07-23T00:58:10+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-05-22&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DALLAS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: AN EMPLOYEE CAME WITH MANAGEMENT EXPERIENCING IRRITATION ON IS SKIN FROM A WET PACKAGE. HE WAS DIRECTED TO RINSE THE AFFECTED AREA WITH WATER. RESPONDER DONNED PPE; BOOTS, GLOVES, GOGGLES AND APRON AND TOOK FULLY STOCKED PRE TRIPPED SPILL CART TO THE SCENE. USING WORD OF MOUTH, SECURED A 15-FOOT HOTZONE AND USED DECISION TREE AND APPROPRIATE RESPONSE SHEET TO CLEAN AND CONTAINERIZE THE SPILL FOR TRANSPORTATION AND PROCESSING IN THE DMP. RESPONDER WAS INFORMED LATER THE EMPLOYEE DROVE HIMSELF TO THE HOSPITAL, MEDICAL CENTER DALLAS.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025052185</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025060066</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025060066&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-07-23T00:58:10+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CENTER&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Central Arkansas Petroleum Transport, Inc&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 35593&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On December 9th, 2024, at approximately 1700, Tyson began refueling procedures for the above ground storage tank. The receiving tank began to overfill due to operator error. Immediately, the Tyson spill response team started laying down absorbent socks around the storm drain and then poured a load of chicken feed to act as an absorbent / berm around the affected area. The diesel fuel was contained on the concrete, but approximately 50 gallons of fuel was in the rock bed surrounding the fuel tank. A hazardous response team (Hopkins Wrecker Service) was notified and arrived on scene at approximately 1830. Hopkins Wrecker Service put down additional dry sweep and absorbent socks. Next, Hopkins used a bobcat to pick up the absorbents, placed them in a lined dumpster, and cleared the soil.  A review of the storm water outfall showed zero signs of an oil sheen and no smell was present. There were no off-site impacts from this release. No personnel were harmed and/or injured. At the time of release, the weather was partly cloudy, and the wind was blowing from the south at 8 mph. The temperature was 70°F and the humidity was 68%.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025060066</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025060064</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025060064&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-07-23T00:58:10+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CHANNELVIEW&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: EQUISTAR CHEMICALS, LP&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 80000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On September 5, 2024, at around 9:35 AM, approximately 14,200 lbs of Ethyl-aluminum dichloride 15% in Hexane (&amp;quot;EADC&amp;quot; herein) were released from the liquid product discharge valve of a tank trailer during a routine unloading operation at the Product Flexibility Unit Unloading Rack. Infrared hydrocarbon detectors detected the released hexane and automatically activated the area deluge system, which suppressed the hydrocarbon vapors and ultimately washed the material into the process sewer collection system, where it was successfully impounded and neutralized prior to discharging. Site emergency response personnel entered the deluged area and stopped the release by closing the air actuated product discharge valve on top of the tanker, which had been found in the open position and not connected to the unloading boom arm. The investigation identified failed barriers and causes leading to the incident and determined that theloading operator had deviated from the unloading procedure by connecting the pressurizing nitrogen to the tanker and actuating air to the product discharge valve, prior to connecting the product unloading boom arm to the trailer. Emergency response personnel found the pneumatic switch for the air actuated product discharge valve in the &amp;quot;OPEN&amp;quot; position, however, the investigation team was not able to conclusively determine how or why the valve was opened. The pneumatic switch for the valve in the &amp;quot;OPEN&amp;quot; position allowed the pressurized EADC to flow to atmosphere. Following interviews with other qualified EADC unloading operators, the investigation team determined that the individual responsible for unloading this trailer deviated from the well-established unloading procedure used in practice. Corrective actions were generated with the intent of addressing the failed barriers and the underlying causes of these failures. The investigation team concluded that while the loader violated well-established and understood safe unloading procedures, the written language of the EADC unloading procedure is unclear and contains unworkable steps due to the above mentioned out of service system.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025060064</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
