<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for CT</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for CT</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 21:13:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024060051</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024060051&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-07-19T18:15:23+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-05-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: NORWALK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: STANDARD PETROLEUM COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On Thursday, 05/02/2024, at approximately 5:25am ET. Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s driver was &amp;#x27; traveling on the 1-95 - southbound in the right lane (of3). As Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s driver approached exit 14 on 1-95 southbound, a black Chevy Camaro struck Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s upper right side as the Camaro driver crossed a solid white line when it merged into traffic. After striking Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s vehicle, the Camaro then struck a trailer traveling parallel to Standard Petroleum m the middle lane, which caused the trailer to strike Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s vehicle. The cause of the failure is still being investigated; however, it is Standard Petroleum s understanding that the trailer struck Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s fuel tank which caused a fuel leak. Since the investigation is ongoing, Standard Petroleum is not able to describe the package failure with specificity at this time. ?nee Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s driver discovered the fuel leak, he immediately called 911 and notified Stand ard Petroleum dispatch of the incident. It is Standard Petroleum&amp;#x27;s unders!anding that either DEEP or Connecticut State Police notified Standard Republic, who is an environmental first responder for the State of Connecticut, to remedy the fuel leak.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024060051</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 18:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
