<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for NM</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for NM</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 01:15:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025050311</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025050311&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-06-10T03:46:53+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-05-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ALBUQUERQUE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ABF FREIGHT SYSTEM, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Forklift driver punctured 1 tote when moving freight. Maree Montoya, 120/ABQ Operations Supervisor,  reported 330 Gallons from 1 tote spilled on dock floor due to a forklift operator puncturing the tote. A crew from Environmental Restoration arrived. Crews placed absorbent pads and absorbent booms t o contain the release on the loading dock. Environmental Restoration personnel utilized a shop-vac to collect freestanding liquid throughout the release site.  Environmental Restoration personnel deployed granular absorbents to the impacted area and worked them in with hand tools. Crews utilized a s hop-vac to transfer the remaining contents of the damaged tote into 55-gallon drums. All alcoholic beverage-impacted material was collected and containerized in five (5) 55-gallon drums and staged on-site for further management. ER personnel noted no further actions required on-site and crews demobi lized.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025050311</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
