<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for ID</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for ID</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:35:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025040470</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025040470&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-05-23T00:57:51+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-07-16&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Rexburg&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: ID&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: KAG MERCHANT GAS GROUP, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 6187&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On July 16, 2024, at 9:30am, Kenan Advantage Group truck and LNG trailer arrived at the Rexburg LNG Facility. IGC Vaporization Technicians (Vap Tech) began preparation for offload. The LNG trailer pressure was increased to approximately 60 psig, the transfer hose was connected to the LNG trailer, the purge valve at the truck Offloading Skid was opened and the hose was purged.  At 10:10am, the Vap Tech slightly opened the LNG trailer fill and drain valve. Vapor and LNG began to release from the vent stack at the back of the LNG trailer. The Vap Tech immediately left the hazardous area and attempted to relieve pressure from the LNG trailer, as it was initially believed the LNG was being released from the LNG trailer relief valve. The emergency shutdown (ESD) at the back of the LNG trailer was in the hazardous area and not accessible.  At 10:15am, a local methane detector at the Offloading Skid alarmed and initiated an emergency shutdown.  At 10:35am, the Vap Tech pushed a secondary ESD, located near the front of the trailer, to close the fire blocks on the LNG trailer. The fire blocks did not shut off and stop the release of LNG resulting in the LNG flowing into the concrete spill pit at the facility.  At 10:45am, the Fire Department arrived onsite, and evacuations began at 11:30am. Seventeen (17) residential buildings (approximately 30 people) were evacuated. The Vap Techs continued to monitor the atmosphere with gas detectors from a safe distance.  At 2:54pm, the area was deemed safe, and the Vap Techs shut in the system.  At 3:30pm, the evacuations were lifted.  At 4:47pm, the Rexburg LNG Facility was returned to normal operation.   Upon incident investigation, it was discovered when the fill and drain valve was slightly opened, the LNG flowed through the fill line bleed valve on the LNG trailer, into the vent piping, and sprayed out of the vent stack. The fill line bleed should have been verified to be closed before opening the fill and drain valve. It was also discovered that the secondary failure of the fire block valve not closing caused the LNG to continue to release into the concrete spill pit.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025040470</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
