<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports, for TN</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration, for TN</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:15:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024120272</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024120272&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-07T00:48:34+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-27&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: MOSHEIM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Holston Gases, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 127250&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver had been making propane deliveries during the remnants of Hurricane Helene.  Weather conditions were rainy with very high gusty winds.  Driver stated that heavy wind gust caught the truck and pushed the truck toward the shoulder of the roadway.  Right side tires dropped off the asphalt and when the driver corrected truck proceeded to overturn in the roadway and rolled coming to a stop on its side.  Impact from the rollover damage one of the vapor return valves on the back of the truck and it started leaking propane.  Area was secured when law enforcement arrived at the scene.  Roadway was closed due to leaking propane.  Fire Department and Greenville TN Hazmat team also responded to the site.   Response team connected a vapor hose to the truck and routed it away from the truck so that vapor could be flared off to reduce the vapor pressure in the tank.  Once the vapor pressure the was reduced the leak subsequently stopped so that the truck could be returned to its wheels and towed from the site.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024120272</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
