<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 21:14:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024110252</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024110252&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-15T12:23:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ANDREWS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PETROLEUM TRANSPORTS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver allowed CTMV to drift onto the right shoulder of the roadway.  The driver over corrected to the left, which caused the CTMV to roll onto its right side.  This caused about a 2 to 3 foot cut into the tank.  Approximately 3,500 gallons of unleaded gasoline spilled onto the shoulder of the roadway.  The Texas Department of Public Safety responded to the scene and notified United Petroleum Transports, Inc.  UPT then contracted an Environmental Clean up Service.  The Environmental Clean up Service went the scene and contained the spill.  It the went through the process of removing the contaminated soil and replacing it with clean soil.  The final remediation was done on 11/11/2024 and report was sent to TXDEQ.  Fortunately, the spill occurred in an unpopulated area so no people, homes, or business were affected.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024110252</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
