<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 18:20:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025050671</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025050671&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-06-01T01:13:35+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-05-07&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: PHILADELPHIA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: PA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Hazmats came back on truck. Another QA admin and I placed damaged hazmats in hazmat bin and placed them in hazmat cage. After packing damages into hazmat bin the other QA admin took glove off using her mouth and later fell ill. The sort manager called 911 for her and she was transported to the hospital for treatment of her condition.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025050671</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 01:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025040652</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025040652&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-06-01T01:13:35+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-04-23&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: TROY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: RANGER LANDSTAR INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 135500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On February 12, 2025, at 0846 ET, Emergency Response and Training Solutions (ERTS) was contacted by Landstar Ranger personnel in Troy, MO regarding a vehicle accident that impacted several cargo products.  Contractors were dispatched to the site to perform all onsite clean-up activities. Upon arrival, contractors found (1) 330-gallon tote of Chlorite solution (UN1908, 8, III), (47) 15-gallon drums of Sodium bisulfate (UN2837, 8, III), and 456 gallons of Citric acid and Copper sulfate pentahydrate (UN1760, 8, III) to be damaged but not leaking. The release was reportedly due to a trailer fire, impacting asphalt and soil. No drains or waterways were impacted by the release. The release was cleaned up with absorbents and the proper PPE. All impacted soil was excavated and backfilled. All waste generated from addressing this release was containerized in (19) roll-offs, (1) 330-gallon tote, and (1) 55-gallon DM which were taken offsite by the contractor for proper disposal. On April 23, 2025, approximately 430 gallons of recovered Sodium bisulfate was transferred into 2 totes. There was 705 gallons of Sodium bisulfate on the BOL - so up to 275 gallons of pH Safe was released or solidified and that is what is included on this report. Again, the confirmed spilled amount of this material was not discovered until April 23, 2025, which is why it is now be reported.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025040652</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 01:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025040634</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025040634&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-06-01T01:13:35+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-04-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LOVELAND&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: WORLD FUEL SERVICES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 35600&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 4/4/2025 at 11:15 EST, a World Fuel Services, Inc. (WFS) Cincinnati Tank Wagon driver was making a delivery to a 3,000-gallon aboveground storage tank (AST) located at Loveland Schools Bus Lot in Loveland, OH. During the delivery, the product started overfilling from the AST vent resulting in an uncontrol release of diesel fuel to the environment at 11:25 EST. The employee, after noticing the spill, ran to shut the pump off and then grabbed spill pads to mitigate the spill. The employee attempted to clean-up spill and contacted WFS Operations. WFS Operations contacted WFS HSE personnel to assist with the incident, spill clean-up, and investigation. The employee did not follow procedures and was not at the point of flow during delivery. The employee was distracted by being on their phone away from the delivery point. Truck camera footage showed two minutes, and thirty-five seconds went by until the employee noticed the release. The employee did not confirm ullage by sticking the tank. The release occurred because of human error. The weather on site that day was on and off again precipitation. This contributed to the spill discharging into the detention pond on site. The calculated release is 165 gallons of No. 2 diesel fuel based on reviewing the truck camera footage.   The spill impacted the parking lot, storm drain, and a 6,000 square foot detention basin/pond. The NRC was notified of the release on 4/4/25 at 18:00 EST. The Ohio EPA was notified of the release on 4/4/2025 at 18:15 EST. The spill was reported to Hamilton County EMA on 4/4/2025 at 18:30 EST. WFS and Ohio EPA met on-site on 4/8/2025 to determine clean-up plan for the detection pond. Ohio EPA approved WFS/HEPACO to treat the basin with in-situ bioremediation and monitoring the site by taking soil samples for VOCs readings until site is clean and no further action is required. Impacted vegetation (leaves/branches) on the ground were removed. Oil booms were placed at the storm drain’s discharge point and at the outfall of the detention pond. Oil booms are being inspected after precipitation events and replaced as needed. HEPACO/WFS will continue to monitor the in-situ bioremediation and inform the Ohio EPA of its progress.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025040634</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 01:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
