<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 01:10:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024110052</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024110052&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-12-11T01:07:09+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-07-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: San Francisco&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AMERICAN AIRLINES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 293807&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Near completion of boarding Flight 2045 a customefs HP Laptop went into thermal runaway in their backpack under the seat near the back of the aircraft. Flames were issuing from the bag as the lithium ion batteries flared. The cabin of the aircraft quickly filled with smoke. The customefs father removed backpack from underseat and successfully bypassed the Flight Attendant and her commands in the aft of the cabin and threw the backpack with flaming laptop out onto the rampat San Francisco(SFO) International airport through one of the aft aircraft emergency exit doorways. Customers were panicking to evacuate. Flight Attendants opened 3 emergency exits on the aircraft and some customers exited slides onto the ramp below while others egressed through the main cabin door back onto the jetway and into the terminal.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024110052</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 01:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024120047</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024120047&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-12-09T12:25:35+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-11-12&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CHEYENNE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: WY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: PIONEER TANK LINES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: The drivers left the shippers facility enroute to the final destination. Upon entering highway traffic, the driver encountered vehicles that were not merging correctly and driving aggressively. They brake checked each other and the truck driver had to do emergency braking maneuver to avoid collision with the 2 other vehicles. The load shifted forward, and 2 IBCs shifted and pushed barrels together after the load securement failed. The drum of ferric chloride was crushed by one of the other barrels, causing a crack at the bottom corner of the barrel. The duration of the release was approximately 1.5 hours. The local fire department was called and was on scene along with WY DOT personnel as it happened at the Wyoming Port of Entry. The Laramie County fire department had sand delivered and built a berm and used absorbent to stop the spread of the spill.  Clean Harbors was contacted by the company to handle the remediation.  The fire department left the scene once the leak stopped and Clean Harbors was enroute from Denver, CO.  Clean Harbors unloaded the trailer in order to find the compromised drum, which was put into a 95-gallon overpack to contain and neutralize it with soda ash.  The crew then decontaminated the trailer using a mix of water and speedy dry.  All waste associated with the decontamination was then shoveled and wiped into a 55-gallon poly drum which was picked up the following day.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024120047</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 12:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024120039</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024120039&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-12-05T12:24:28+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-11-26&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Darlington&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: SC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ESTES EXPRESS LINES&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 6800&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Forklift strike&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024120039</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024120005</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024120005&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-12-05T12:24:28+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-23&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Townville&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: SC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: THE WHITAKER COMPANY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 6365&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver after crossing a rough portion of I-85 noticed a mist in his mirror. He subsequently stopped as soon as possible pulling off the roadway, and off the shoulder as well to investigate. Noticed product Leaking from the rear of his trailer(approx 1/2 gal per min). He placed the absorbent pads he had, to catch what he could and notified his supervisor. His supervisor immediately notified TWC regulatory dept. We then determined what was Leaking and reached out to our response company whom notified DHEC and located a company who could respond. We decided to send personnel from our Spartanburg facility with more pads and catch containers. They arrived before the response company and were able to move some material around on the trailer and where able to close the valve on the IBC and re-secure the dust cap on the tote. They then started using pads to absorb what product they could, as DHEC and the Response company arrived. They then took over assessing the impact and cleanup of the lost material.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024120005</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
