<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:43:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010240</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010240&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-23T21:13:01+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-14&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: PARMA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: PITT OHIO EXPRESS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Upon arrival at the destination terminal, this tote was discovered leaking inside the trailer. The tote was immediately turned on it&amp;#x27;s side to prevent further release. After investigation, it was determined that this tote was damaged due to a load shift during transit. An empty tote was used as dunnage to protect the tote and a piece of wood on the skid broke and was pushed into the tote, causing puncture. The material was a thick liquid and was contained to the trailer floor. The material was absorbed using absorbent material and placed into an overpack container for later disposal.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010240</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010200</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010200&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-23T21:13:01+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-10&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CHICAGO HEIGHTS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: IL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 20000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: XPO Logistics terminal BCH experienced a UN3082 Rhonox Herbicide release from a 275-gallon poly tote. ERTS dispatched contractors to conduct cleanup operations. Contractors arrived onsite and confirmed approximately 165-gallons of product released due to a forklift puncture. The entire trailer floor, a 150’ x 30’ area of the concrete lot below, and 4 drains and 1 catch basin were impacted. All drains lead to the catch basin where the material was contained. The crew utilized a vac truck to remove the product from the catch basin and drains leading to it. Absorbents were deployed to the trailer and concrete lot and worked in. Once the drains were done, absorbent boom was placed in them to collect any residual material. The product remaining the damaged tote was pumped out and the damaged tote was cut up and containerized. Crew returned to site and inspected the drains and flushed and vacuumed them out again. Additional wastewater was generated to be offloaded into totes. Samples were collected to confirm that no residual material remains in the catch basin and samples were collected from the nearby retention pond as well as a precaution. All wastewater was offloaded into totes and all solid cleanup debris was containerized into 55-gallon poly drums. The waste was staged onsite for terminal personnel to manage&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010200</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010224</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010224&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-23T21:13:01+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: GROVE CITY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Pitt Ohio Express&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: As the material was being loaded into a trailer at the destination terminal, a piece of protruding metal from another skid was accidentally pushed into the tote causing damage. The released material was contained to the trailer using neutralizer and absorbent material. The neutralizer and absorbent material was placed into an overpack for proper disposal. The IBC container was also turned on it&amp;#x27;s side as soon as possible to prevent further release of material.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010224</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
