<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:25:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024090068</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024090068&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-10-03T09:21:57+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-26&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Los Angeles&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SINGAPORE AIRLINES LIMITED&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: No&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Agent, Andre Senior, was locating the shipment into the third level of the warehouse racks. When one box fell from the skid while being positioned into racks. Once box fell then it started emanating smoke as it was being burnt. Our Warehouse Manager, Julio Galvez actioned upon seeing this situation happening and box was segregated by our warehouse supervisor, Miguel Lopez, and taken outside of the warehouse for any other reaction from the DG.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024090068</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024100035</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024100035&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-10-03T09:21:57+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Peoria Heights&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: IL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CENTRAL TRANSPORT INTERNATIONAL, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 16250&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Other fell&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024100035</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024090587</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024090587&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-10-02T09:14:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ELBERTON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: GA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AIR PRODUCTS AND CHEMICALS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 300000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On September 2, 2024 at 0545, a Conyers driver was offloading a liquid oxygen trailer at a remote customer site in northern Georgia. Toward the end of the offload, the driver noticed a small fire beginning near the pump area of the trailer. The driver walked around to the outer side of the trailer to investigate and noticed the fire increasing. The driver immediately shut down the offload, and secured the trailer and customer tanks as he exited the area. Please note that at the time of the event, we were unsure that there was an unintentional release of product. Due to the evacuation, we proactively called the NRC, but have determined that there was no release of product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024090587</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024090553</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024090553&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-09-27T09:15:13+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-08-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Marion&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: VMV 05 INC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 56435&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: A semi truck tipped over, hitting a reflector post while taking NB Highway 52 ramp from WB Interstate 90. The incident was reported to the authorities and an emergency response team was called to help. Bay West field staff arrived on site and checked with Olmstead County Hazmat Team and Rochester Fire. A safety briefing was held prior to any assessment or cleanup activities began.  Two field staff suited up in level B PPE to make and initial assessment of the spill. During the initial incident assessment, the semi truck was observed to have overturned onto its side on the Hwy 52 Northbound ramp. The totes and drums within the trailer were flipped from their original position and were sitting with the openings resting on the roof of the trailer. The contents of some of the containers were observed to be still leaking onto the trailer and running out into the vegetation within the right of the way. A large plume of vapor was observed exiting a hole within the roof of the trailer due to a reaction from the chemicals. (It is believed that the vapor was from the non-hazmat products). Entry into the trailer was made to collect PH sample from the products on the floor, assess damage to the containers, and take an inventory of the contents.  Due to the products still gassing, causing a plume of vapor, a confined space fan was set up to vent out the trailer while staff were working. After the initial assessment was conducted, a cleanup plan was made to pump out and transfer the container into new totes. Field Staff began setting up and prepares to transfer the remaining product from the containers. Two staff made entry into the trailer and began to make openings into the hydrogen peroxide totes so a stinger pipe could be used to reach the bottom. Once all of the hydrogen peroxide totes were transferred, 55 gallons of water were flushed through the hoses and pump to decontaminate it before moving onto the next product. After the flush, field staff continued the same process to the remaining products within the trailer until all the totes were empty.  A second crew arrived on site to relieve the initial response crew. A safety briefing  was conducted along with a discussion about the remaining work prior to the first crew mobilizing off site. The second crew began with recovering and overpacking the remaining drums within the trailer. Four drums were still intact, three of the drums were observed to be compromised and damaged, and one drum was empty. The three compromised drums were overpacked and prepared for transport. Once all of the drums were removed, absorbent pads were used to recover any remaining product from the trailer. After all of the product was removed from the trailer, a wrecking crew arrived to upright the semi and move it off site to their storage yard. All of the drums and the waste product that was transferred into totes was delivered to a MnDOT facility in Stewartville until disposal could be arranged. The total transferred product tota&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024090553</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
