<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 06:29:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025040006</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025040006&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-04-20T00:57:38+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DALLAS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: ESTES EXPRESS LINES&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 8500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Clean Harbors personnel arrived onsite and observed an estimated two hundred seventy-five (275) gallons were released from a two hundred seventy-five (275) gallon IBC plastic tote. It affected 100’-by-20’ area of concrete and a 3’-by-3’ area of trailer floor. It was damaged in the mechanical shop then placed on the trailer. Clean Harbors advised the mechanical shop that it needed pressure washed and flushed down the oil water separator. Granular absorbents were deployed to the affected areas. Clean Harbors then transferred seventy-five (75) gallons of remaining product into a new IBC plastic tote. It was then determined there were two hundred (200) gallons released. The generated waste was four (4) 55-gallon metal drums containing impacted absorbents and one (1) 85-gallon metal drum containing absorbents and cut up tote. The generated waste was staged onsite and will remain onsite for the ESTES DGRM team to coordinate disposal. The ESTES terminal supervisor approved all work before Hepaco departed.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025040006</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 00:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
