<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 12:23:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024110059</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024110059&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-07T12:22:36+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-11-05&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: INDIANAPOLIS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: IN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 8500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: At 0304 ET, XPO notified ERTS of a cargo release at terminal BIN. It was reported that approximately 220-gallons of UN1903 released from a plastic tote due to a forklift puncture. The release impacted concrete dock floor.  Contractors arrived on site applying absorbent to solidify the impacted areas of the dock floor.  All spent absorbent and debris were containerized into (7) 55-gallon metal drums.  Contractors used poly containers to recoup good product which was then transferred into a new 275-gallon tote - (approximately 150-gallons of product).  The waste was staged onsite for terminal to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024110059</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 12:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024110016</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024110016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-07T12:22:36+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-09&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: El Cajon&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: COASTAL TRANSPORT CO.,. INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 2607950&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: CTMV was stopped at traffic signal on Navaho Road. When the light turned green, the operator began accelerating to make 90 degree left tum onto Fletcher Parkway. The tum is an&amp;quot;off-camber turn&amp;quot; as the outer tum radius surface is lower than the inner tum radius. The driver failed to respond correctly to this surface condition. As the CTMV turned, the liquid cargo surged to the passenger side of the cargo compartments. The sudden weight shift caused the CTMV to roll over to the right. The CTMV rotated 180 degrees clockwise and came to rest upside down straddling the roadway and sidewalk. Fuel began Ieaking through the venting devices mounted between the rollover rails on the top of the semi-trailer. The fuel flowed downhill along the sidewalk and curb. Fuel entered two storm drain entry points before the entry points were closed by sand bagging. The storm drain was dry down stream. While upside down, the compartments were tapped, and approximately 400 gallons were recovered from the compartments. Fuel recovery and remediation steps were begun immediately. Approximately 1500 gallons were recovered from a concrete utility pit located within the sidewalk underneath the upside down CTMV. The remaining fuel is being recovered by cleaning the storm drain conduit and replacing soil that has absorbed fuel downstream from the spill site. Asphalt roadway surface is being replaced for approximately 200 feet downhill from the spill site. The fuel did not enter any waterway.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024110016</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 12:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024100689</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024100689&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-05T12:22:11+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-01&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SPRING HILL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: FL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AMERIGAS PROPANE, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 115050&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: S&amp;amp;L Company Transport driver started his workday at 1753 on 9/31/2024. He drove from his parking location at 15222 Hudson Ave., Spring Hill, FL to the Orlando, FL terminal to load his truck. He made two deliveries - the first being in Palmetto, FL at an AmeriGas facility, and the last being in Clearwater a the AmeriGas facility. When Transport Driver completed the final delivery in Clearwater, he drove back to his parking location at 15222 Hudson Ave., Spring Hill, FL, which is an AmeriGas property.   To access this location, the Transport Driver backs in off the roadway to get into the yard. On this morning at 0522, he pulled up headed westbound on Hudson Ave. and began his backing maneuver traveling 3 mph. He was across both lanes of traffic in the middle of his maneuver when a 3rd party vehicle traveling eastbound on Hudson Ave. crashed into the transport trailer. The Transport Driver immediately got out of the vehicle to assess the situation and called 911.   When emergency personnel arrived on scene, the scene was secured and the leak was assessed. There was a small leak coming from the flange of the pump under the transport and emergency personnel and AmeriGas decided it would be best to evacuate the remaining propane in the transport by flaring it off. The responding fire dept. utilized water spray to dissipate some of the propane vapor under the transport before they were able to flare. The leak lasted for roughly 2 hours before flaring equipment could be set up and utilized. The flare was set up and remaining propane was burnt off prior to the transport and 3rd party vehicle being moved and the road re-opened.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024100689</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2024100114</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2024100114&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-05T12:22:11+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-13&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: KINGSPORT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SINDLE TRUCKING, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 76044&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: BAE Systems Ordnance Systems Inc. (OSI) is the operating contractor for Holston Army Ammunition  Plant (HSAAP) located at 4509 West Stone Drive in Kingsport, Hawkins County, Tennessee. On  September 13, 2024 a hose rupture during offload of a strong nitric acid tanker resulted in a  release of acid to the environment. A description of the event is outlined below:  The truck driver and operators started the transfer and then moved to observe from a safe location  per standard operating procedure. Approximately 10 minutes after the transfer started, personnel  observed a NOx cloud and nitric acid spray coming from the back of the tanker. After the wind  shifted, the driver made the decision to approach the tanker and activate the emergency stop,  ending the release. Upon further investigation after the incident, personnel found the transfer  hose had failed.  The total amount of nitric acid released from the tanker was 20,988 pounds. It is estimated that  approximately 10,494 pounds of nitric acid drained to the spill basin for the tanker pad and into  the wastewater collection system. Approximately 10,494 pounds sprayed onto the ground next to the  tanker pad. None of the nitric acid traveled to the stormwater channels. Approximately 105 pounds  of NOx was released during the event. A hazmat contractor was promptly hired to clean up the release.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2024100114</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024100734</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024100734&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-05T00:41:19+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-06-16&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DUCHESNE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: UT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: MARATHON PETROLEUM COMPANY LP&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: During the loading process, the correct pressure release valves were not open and allowed for a build up of pressure to crack the welded seams.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024100734</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024100731</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024100731&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-04T12:23:29+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-10-26&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Vernon&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SAIA MOTOR FREIGHT LINE, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 15000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Other fell&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024100731</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024100736</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024100736&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2024-11-04T12:23:29+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-21&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DONNA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: LOVE'S TRAVEL STOPS &amp; COUNTRY STORES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 45500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: It was reported that 495-gallons of gasoline was released impacting a impervious surface of approximately 150’-by-150’, and nearby storm drains that outfall to the onsite retention pond. All the manways and retention pond were checked to verify no fuel had left the property. E3OMI pumped all of the liquid from the storm drains and basin. 21,840-gallons of gasoline impacted water was recovered and processed for recycling.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024100736</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 12:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
