<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024120272</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024120272&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-07T00:48:34+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-09-27&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: MOSHEIM&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Holston Gases, Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 127250&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver had been making propane deliveries during the remnants of Hurricane Helene.  Weather conditions were rainy with very high gusty winds.  Driver stated that heavy wind gust caught the truck and pushed the truck toward the shoulder of the roadway.  Right side tires dropped off the asphalt and when the driver corrected truck proceeded to overturn in the roadway and rolled coming to a stop on its side.  Impact from the rollover damage one of the vapor return valves on the back of the truck and it started leaking propane.  Area was secured when law enforcement arrived at the scene.  Roadway was closed due to leaking propane.  Fire Department and Greenville TN Hazmat team also responded to the site.   Response team connected a vapor hose to the truck and routed it away from the truck so that vapor could be flared off to reduce the vapor pressure in the tank.  Once the vapor pressure the was reduced the leak subsequently stopped so that the truck could be returned to its wheels and towed from the site.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024120272</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025011298</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025011298&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-04T06:26:27+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Longview&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Union Pacific Railroad&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 5000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: ***Upon notification, I contacted Code 3 to respond with a crew and I was enroute.  I was advised by yard personnel that the cloud was on the top of the car and would &amp;quot;cycle&amp;quot;, starting and stopping, and all personnel were clear of the area and there was no movement in the yard, except for the mainline.  Upon Code 3 arrival, the car was assessed and determined to have a PRD instead of a rupture disc.  The leak was coming from the liquid connection flange, there was no cloud and was wisping out faintly.  Code 3 exited the car and updated me.  I contacted Reagent Chemical and advised him of the incident and was provided photos of how the flange should look with a gasket visible between the red and black spacers.  Code 3 climbed the car and completed a more thorough inspection and found that the liquid flange bolts were easily turned by hand and no gasket was visible.  The bolts were tightened and the off gassing slowed.  There was moisture in the air which reacted with the HCL vapor and created a pH of 1 on top of the liquid line.  The car was decontaminated with soda ash and water and the off gassing stopped.  The car was moved to the Rip track, yard operations resumed, and there was no off gassing during the move.  The air flange was removed to check for pressure and a vacuum was on the car.  Then the liquid flange and spacer was removed, no gasket was installed, so a neoprene gasket was installed, and the liquid flange and spacer reinstalled.  No further issues.  Reagent Chemical sent a certified repair personnel out the afternoon of 1/29/25, installed a new gasket, checked the car for other issues, and prepped the car for Home Shop.  Car is still in HZ hold.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025011298</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025011249</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025011249&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-04T06:26:27+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ARCADIA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FIRST CLASS SERVICES, INCORPORATED&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 169100&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 12-30-2024 at 1420 hours central time I was notified by our driver that he had overturned his truck while pulling a load of Creosote. He was traveling south on Missouri Hwy 21, near Arcadia, MO, and when negotiating a left curve traveled partially off the west edge of roadway, onto a soft shoulder. In an attempt to regain control, he overcorrected, lost control and overturned onto the passenger side. The rear head fastened to the side wall of tanker (231) wall ruptured, causing more than 30,000 lbs. of material to leak onto the ground, and continued to leak for approximately five hours.   The commodity being transported was Creosote, UN 3082 a Class 9 hazard. Emergency services, Pilot Knob Fire Protection District, Missouri Hwy Patrol, and Missouri DOT Hazmat Team (MDOTHT) arrived on scene. The Missouri state EPA was contacted, and I spoke with Sharon Kennedy and Greg Dillon informing them of all updates. I contacted the National Response Center (NRC) to report on the chemical spill and was provided an incident number (1420166). In addition, I was contacted by Liam Hazen, who is the disaster coordinator for the MODNR Environmental Emergency Response Section. He provided a list of hazardous material contractor cleanup teams.   At approximately 1720 hours central I contacted Environmental Restoration LLC; an environmental clean-up team located near St Louis and spoke with their representative, William Lieneke, and he accepted the agreement to conduct the cleanup. Upon arriving on scene, William Lieneke made an evaluation and operated an excavator to build a berm to block the creosote from draining into a nearby stream. Lieneke has filed with the state to obtain the required permits to initiate the removal and disposal of the Creosote.  At approximately 0149 hours Mr. Lieneke informed me he received authority from the state DNR representative to turn the truck and trailer from the side to the upright position. Trailer (231) was no longer leaking material due to hardening.  At approximately 0410 hours the remaining Creosote was pumped off the damaged tanker (231) and onto a replacement tanker and truck.  The remaining material was then transported back to the facility of origin, Omaha Track located in Granite City, Illinois.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025011249</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025010092</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025010092&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-01T00:52:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-20&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CROMWELL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CITY OIL CO., INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Upon exiting to the off ramp truck hit a ice patch weather conditions were below zero temp.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025010092</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024120147</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024120147&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-01T00:52:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-03&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: PARIS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: AT THE UPS FACILITY IN ROISSY, FRANCE, ONE AIR PACKAGE FROM CANADA TO FRANCE WAS BEING LOADED ONTO A PALLET FOR THE FINAL DELIVERY DESTINATION WHEN AN EXPLOSIVE SOUND WAS HEARD FOLLOWED BY SMOKE EMITTING FROM THE PACKAGE. THE FACILITY WAS PROMPTLY EVACUATED FOR APPROXIMATELY ONE HALF HOUR. THE LOCAL FIRE BRIGADE AND AIRPORT POLICE, AIR TRANSPORT GENDARMERIE (GTA) RESPONDED TO THE EVENT.  PACKAGE INSPECTION REVEALS ONE ECO COUNTER URBAN POST (PEOPLE COUNTING SYSTEM) CONTAINING AN INSTALLED LITHIUM METAL BATTERY. THERE IS EVIDENCE OF A THERMAL LITHIUM BATTERY EVENT HAVING OCCURRED AS EVIDENT BY THE CHARRING AND BURNING MARKS ON THE DEVICE.  THE PACKAGE WAS CONFISCATED BY THE GENDARMERIE DES TRANSPORTS AERIENS (GTA) FOR ANALYSIS. ONE EMPLOYEE HAD RINGING IN THE EARS AND WAS SENT TO THE HOSPITAL FOR EVALUATION. THE EMPLOYEE WAS RELEASED AND GIVEN THREE SICK LEAVE DAYS. THE PACKAGE WAS A RETURN SERVICE PACKAGE SHIPPED FROM CANADA TO THE PRODUCT OWNER IN FRANCE.  THE OWNER OF THE UPS ACCOUNT IS 82F81F, ECO COMPTEUR, 4 RUE CHARLES BOURSEUL, LANNION FRANCE 22300. THE PACKAGE ENTERED THE NETWORK ON 18-NOV AND WAS FLOWN ON UPS AIRCRAFT YYZ TO SDF, SDF TO PHL, AND PHL TO CDG. THE PACKAGE ARRIVED IN CDG ON 20-NOV AND WAS NOT RELEASED FROM CUSTOMS UNTIL 02-DEC. NRC REPORT WAS MADE ON 06-DEC AS REQUIRED 171.15, NRC 1418132.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024120147</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
