<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 06:18:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025011298</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025011298&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-04T06:26:27+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Longview&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TX&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: Union Pacific Railroad&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 5000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: ***Upon notification, I contacted Code 3 to respond with a crew and I was enroute.  I was advised by yard personnel that the cloud was on the top of the car and would &amp;quot;cycle&amp;quot;, starting and stopping, and all personnel were clear of the area and there was no movement in the yard, except for the mainline.  Upon Code 3 arrival, the car was assessed and determined to have a PRD instead of a rupture disc.  The leak was coming from the liquid connection flange, there was no cloud and was wisping out faintly.  Code 3 exited the car and updated me.  I contacted Reagent Chemical and advised him of the incident and was provided photos of how the flange should look with a gasket visible between the red and black spacers.  Code 3 climbed the car and completed a more thorough inspection and found that the liquid flange bolts were easily turned by hand and no gasket was visible.  The bolts were tightened and the off gassing slowed.  There was moisture in the air which reacted with the HCL vapor and created a pH of 1 on top of the liquid line.  The car was decontaminated with soda ash and water and the off gassing stopped.  The car was moved to the Rip track, yard operations resumed, and there was no off gassing during the move.  The air flange was removed to check for pressure and a vacuum was on the car.  Then the liquid flange and spacer was removed, no gasket was installed, so a neoprene gasket was installed, and the liquid flange and spacer reinstalled.  No further issues.  Reagent Chemical sent a certified repair personnel out the afternoon of 1/29/25, installed a new gasket, checked the car for other issues, and prepped the car for Home Shop.  Car is still in HZ hold.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025011298</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025011249</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025011249&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-04T06:26:27+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-30&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ARCADIA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FIRST CLASS SERVICES, INCORPORATED&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 169100&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On 12-30-2024 at 1420 hours central time I was notified by our driver that he had overturned his truck while pulling a load of Creosote. He was traveling south on Missouri Hwy 21, near Arcadia, MO, and when negotiating a left curve traveled partially off the west edge of roadway, onto a soft shoulder. In an attempt to regain control, he overcorrected, lost control and overturned onto the passenger side. The rear head fastened to the side wall of tanker (231) wall ruptured, causing more than 30,000 lbs. of material to leak onto the ground, and continued to leak for approximately five hours.   The commodity being transported was Creosote, UN 3082 a Class 9 hazard. Emergency services, Pilot Knob Fire Protection District, Missouri Hwy Patrol, and Missouri DOT Hazmat Team (MDOTHT) arrived on scene. The Missouri state EPA was contacted, and I spoke with Sharon Kennedy and Greg Dillon informing them of all updates. I contacted the National Response Center (NRC) to report on the chemical spill and was provided an incident number (1420166). In addition, I was contacted by Liam Hazen, who is the disaster coordinator for the MODNR Environmental Emergency Response Section. He provided a list of hazardous material contractor cleanup teams.   At approximately 1720 hours central I contacted Environmental Restoration LLC; an environmental clean-up team located near St Louis and spoke with their representative, William Lieneke, and he accepted the agreement to conduct the cleanup. Upon arriving on scene, William Lieneke made an evaluation and operated an excavator to build a berm to block the creosote from draining into a nearby stream. Lieneke has filed with the state to obtain the required permits to initiate the removal and disposal of the Creosote.  At approximately 0149 hours Mr. Lieneke informed me he received authority from the state DNR representative to turn the truck and trailer from the side to the upright position. Trailer (231) was no longer leaking material due to hardening.  At approximately 0410 hours the remaining Creosote was pumped off the damaged tanker (231) and onto a replacement tanker and truck.  The remaining material was then transported back to the facility of origin, Omaha Track located in Granite City, Illinois.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025011249</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025010092</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025010092&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-01T00:52:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-20&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: CROMWELL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CITY OIL CO., INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Upon exiting to the off ramp truck hit a ice patch weather conditions were below zero temp.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025010092</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024120147</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024120147&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-02-01T00:52:02+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-03&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: PARIS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: UNITED PARCEL SERVICE CO.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: AT THE UPS FACILITY IN ROISSY, FRANCE, ONE AIR PACKAGE FROM CANADA TO FRANCE WAS BEING LOADED ONTO A PALLET FOR THE FINAL DELIVERY DESTINATION WHEN AN EXPLOSIVE SOUND WAS HEARD FOLLOWED BY SMOKE EMITTING FROM THE PACKAGE. THE FACILITY WAS PROMPTLY EVACUATED FOR APPROXIMATELY ONE HALF HOUR. THE LOCAL FIRE BRIGADE AND AIRPORT POLICE, AIR TRANSPORT GENDARMERIE (GTA) RESPONDED TO THE EVENT.  PACKAGE INSPECTION REVEALS ONE ECO COUNTER URBAN POST (PEOPLE COUNTING SYSTEM) CONTAINING AN INSTALLED LITHIUM METAL BATTERY. THERE IS EVIDENCE OF A THERMAL LITHIUM BATTERY EVENT HAVING OCCURRED AS EVIDENT BY THE CHARRING AND BURNING MARKS ON THE DEVICE.  THE PACKAGE WAS CONFISCATED BY THE GENDARMERIE DES TRANSPORTS AERIENS (GTA) FOR ANALYSIS. ONE EMPLOYEE HAD RINGING IN THE EARS AND WAS SENT TO THE HOSPITAL FOR EVALUATION. THE EMPLOYEE WAS RELEASED AND GIVEN THREE SICK LEAVE DAYS. THE PACKAGE WAS A RETURN SERVICE PACKAGE SHIPPED FROM CANADA TO THE PRODUCT OWNER IN FRANCE.  THE OWNER OF THE UPS ACCOUNT IS 82F81F, ECO COMPTEUR, 4 RUE CHARLES BOURSEUL, LANNION FRANCE 22300. THE PACKAGE ENTERED THE NETWORK ON 18-NOV AND WAS FLOWN ON UPS AIRCRAFT YYZ TO SDF, SDF TO PHL, AND PHL TO CDG. THE PACKAGE ARRIVED IN CDG ON 20-NOV AND WAS NOT RELEASED FROM CUSTOMS UNTIL 02-DEC. NRC REPORT WAS MADE ON 06-DEC AS REQUIRED 171.15, NRC 1418132.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024120147</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010368</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010368&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-24&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Erlanger&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: KY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AVERITT EXPRESS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 10100&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Load Shift&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010368</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010354</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010354&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-23&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Muskogee&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: R&amp;L CARRIERS SHARED SERVICES, L.L.C.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 6500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Improperly strapped for transit.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010354</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025011023</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025011023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-21&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: MEMPHIS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Air&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: no comment provided&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025011023</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010291</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010291&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-17&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: RIVERVIEW&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: MI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: VEOLIA ES TECHNICAL SOLUTIONS, L.L.C.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: On January 17th, 2025, at 12:34, a three-person Veolia team was conducting operations at the ASH Stevens customer site. The Veolia employees were in the process of loading totes onto a box truck using an electric pallet jack. The Veolia box truck was positioned at the customer&amp;#x27;s loading dock.  During the loading procedure, an incident occurred when a tote situated near the front of the box truck (one of the first to be loaded) was accidentally punctured. This happened as the pallet jack operator was attempting to place a second tote behind it, towards the rear/open end of the truck.  The puncture occurred in the left-hand lower quadrant of the 275-gallon tote. As a result, the contents began to leak, flowing from the front of the box truck towards the rear while it was still in the loading dock. The leaking material spilled off the truck and into the customer&amp;#x27;s secondary containment system, where it was successfully contained.  The customer&amp;#x27;s team promptly responded to the situation by transferring the remaining contents of the damaged tote into a new, undamaged container. They also managed to recover the spilled material from the secondary containment area. It is estimated that less than 250 gallons of the material was lost to the customer&amp;#x27;s containment system.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010291</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010312</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010312&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-04&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EDWARDSVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: KS&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDEX FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Associate punctured freight with forklift blades while loading / unloading causing product to leak&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010312</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010369</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010369&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-03&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: EAST BRUNSWICK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NJ&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: A. DUIE PYLE INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 9700&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: When unloading freight from trailer forklift operator was carrying the tote on the forkblades of the forklift. As the forklift was transitioning from the trailer to the dock over the dock plate the IBC started to wobble on the forkblades. The forklift operator tried to move forward back on to the trailer and when doing so the IBC fell over causing the lid to partially rupture contributing to the unintentional release. Defensive actions were immediately taken to contain the spilled material and an outside spill response company was dispatched to aid in mitigating and cleaning up the spilled material. The spilled material was cleaned up by an outside company and placed into multiple recovery containers for disposal.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010369</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025010309</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025010309&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-01-02&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: LITTLE ROCK&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: AR&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDEX FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Associate did not block and/or brace freight properly for transport.  Freight was crushed causing release of product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025010309</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025010073</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025010073&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-16&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: MACON&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: GA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: CARDINAL HEALTH 414, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: While driving eastbound(speed unknown) on Highway 74 at approximately 6:00 AM on 12/16/2024, the vehicle hit a cow that was in the middle of the road. The driver reported heavy fog at the time of the collision. As a result of the collision, the vehicle left the roadway onto the eastbound shoulder of the road and burst into flames. The driver escaped the vehicle and called emergency medical services. h Upon theif arrival on the scene shortly after the accident, law enforcement closed the eastbound lane of the road. This lane of the road remained closed for several hours until being reopened following decontamination of the area in the evening on December 16. After the vehicle caught fire, the flames consumed the vehicle, 6reaching the shipping container and several of the unit dose shields and spreading some radioactive contamination in the general vicinity of the vehicle. EMS worked to extinguish the fire and in doing so, spread some contamination further around the area, reaching approximately 15-20 feet away from the vehicle. Two of the unit dose pigs were later identified in the debris, while another two items that may have been unit dose pigs were also identified. The other pigs appear to have fully melted in the fire and their materials released. It was not possible to identify which specific doses&amp;#x27; pigs were intact. Cleanup was conducted by a contractor, Alpha-Omega Training&amp;amp; Compliance, Inc., with direction by Cardinal Health and a representative from the Georgia DNR Radioactive Materials Program. The area was found to be at background levels after cleanup concluded on the evening of 12/16.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025010073</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2024120454</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2024120454&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-01-31T00:56:40+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-01&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: DUCHESNE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: UT&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: MARATHON PETROLEUM COMPANY LP&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: During the loading process, the loading hose burst which resulted in the release of product.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2024120454</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
