<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest PHMSA Hazardous Materials Incident Reports</title>
    <link>https://github.com/data-liberation-project/phma-hazmat-incident-reports</link>
    <description>The latest Form 5800.1 hazardous material reports submitted to the Department of Transportation and posted online by the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030167</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030167&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: NASHVILLE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: TN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS FREIGHT, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 21500&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: XPO-Logistics contacted ERTS regarding a punctured tote containing hazardous product, BONDERITE C-AK ZX-1 ALKALINE CLEANER. A contractor dispatched and observed an estimated 200-gallon release onto the concrete dock floor and parking lot in a 100’x70’ area as a result of a forklift puncture. Oil dry was applied to the released material and a tote transfer was performed for the residual product left inside of the damaged tote. In total, 23 drums of waste were generated from this response that were taken by the contractor and staged at their location for waste management. The customer refused the new tote with the transferred product, so XPO staged the tote in the waste area for waste disposal. No storm-drains, waterways, or soil were involved in this incident.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030167</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030168</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030168&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-03-08&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Avon&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: KEPICH TRANSPORTATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver did not secure back dome lid &amp;amp; was notified it was leaking via phone call. Driver stopped as soon as they told him and that&amp;#x27;s when spillage occurred. Facility quickly cleaned up the spillage &amp;amp; surfaces. Est. 3 hour clean up&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030168</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025030140</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025030140&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: GRAYSLAKE&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: IL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FEDERAL EXPRESS CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: attachment Name:US-1X-920512-01-AQUA BALANCE MURIATIC ACID.pdf&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025030140</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030059</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030059&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-27&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Hanover Park&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: IL&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: SAIA MOTOR FREIGHT LINE, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 6000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Forklift strike&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030059</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030046</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030046&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-16&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: TOOMSBORO&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: GA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: FLORIDA ROCK &amp; TANK LINES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 295000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: This was a single vehicle accident in which our driver gradually left the roadway onto the slopped shoulder area.  the driver attempted to return the vehicle onto the roadway, this initiated the rollover sequence. The trailer came to rest upside down which allowed the product to spill from multiple dome lids.    The driver sustained life threatening  injuries and was transported to the hospital where he was pronounced deceased.  It us unknown why the driver left the roadway.    This was reported to the National Response Center #1423708&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030046</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report X-2025030170</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report X-2025030170&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ATTICA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: OH&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Rail&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: NORFOLK SOUTHERN CORPORATION&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 3600000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: NS train 18ML811 pulling east on Main #1 near Attica, OH derailed 20 cars. The derailment led to the release of 5800 gallons of &amp;quot;alcohols, n.o.s.&amp;quot; from tank car TILX360188 due to 2 manway bolts being sheared off and the release of 20 gallons of alcohols, &amp;quot;n.o.s.&amp;quot; from tank car TILX198831 from the closed BOV after the BOV nipple was sheared off.  The total cost for both releases will be recorded on this report for TILX360188. The total cost estimate is $3,600,00.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:X-2025030170</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025020243</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025020243&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: San Jose&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: CA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: AIR PRODUCTS AND CHEMICALS, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 253900&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Driver was traveling about 7 mph while attempting to make a U-turn on a remote road. Tires on passenger side of trailer entered soft shoulder causing trailer to roll. There were no 3rd parties, no injuries, and some damage to barbwire fence and street sign. Crisis Center was notified and activated. Local Vehicle Recovery Teams from Galt and Santa Clara have responded to the scene. Local fire department responded to scene. Corporate Safety and Environmental notified. Our Air Products driver arrived at the scheduled delivery location with a fully loaded Nitrogen trailer when he approached a gate. The driver exited his vehicle and quickly determined he was at the wrong location. Upon returning to his vehicle, he decided to perform a U-Turn on a narrow two-lane road which had an incline. During the maneuvering, the back end of the trailer dug into soft shoulder and mud, the weight of the trailer pushed the tractor which caused the trailer to break away from the 5th wheel and roll against the tractor. The trailer then rolled over onto its side across the roadway. The trailer released liquid Nitrogen due to the PSV line being damaged. During the roll over event, the tractor’s fuel tank was ruptured causing a diesel spill onto the ground. There were no injuries reported, and no other vehicles involved in this incident.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025020243</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025020052</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025020052&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-11&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SHARPSBURG&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: PA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: PENN TANK LINES, INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 165400&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Truck driver lost control of vehicle, struck cement barrier on side of roadway. Driver over corrected causing the trailer to sway, then rollover. Unit remained on roadway and no other vehicles were involved. This trailer consisted of 4 compartments. The last compartment received a puncture spilling 2,000 gals. of ULSD B2. The product ran down the roadway and entered storm drains that discharged rain fall into Pine Creek. Pine Creek discharges into The Allegheny River approximately 1 /2 mile downstream from the spill. The duration of the release was immediate &amp;amp; flowed freely until fire department was on scene. The trailer was an aluminum MC 306 built by Custom in the year 1995.  Multiple fire departments were on scene along with the PA State Police, Allegheny County Hazmat, Etna Baro Police and others. On initial impact a fire started from product spilled along the barrier wall when contacted and ruptured. The fire department extinguished with no incident. The driver exited from the cab on his own, transported to ER and released with no injuries other than a cut on his hand. The fire departments blocked the drains with booms and other material to stop any continuous flow that could occur. A HM Spill Contractor was called to remove the remaining ULSD from the other 3 compartments. The trailer needed to be drilled to install a pump out hose into the tank. Product was transferred without further incident. The contractor was completing cleanup while the action of pumping the trailer was done. After the truck was righted and removed from the scene under tow, the contractor continued with the cleanup under the supervision of the PennDOT responder. Fire crews installed booms in the creek and at the mouth where the creek empties into the Allegheny River. The creek and river are an ongoing project to retain and remove product. Multiple state and local agencies are involved in monitoring the spill cleanup actions.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025020052</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report E-2025030151</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report E-2025030151&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-16T21:12:33+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2025-02-10&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: ALLENTOWN&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: PA&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: XPO LOGISTICS, LLC&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 50000&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: t 0415 ET, XPO notified ERTS of a cargo release at XAN. It was reported that approximately 100 gallons of Enviroset 40E FNB Resin were released from a 275-gallon plastic tote due to improper loading by XAN. The release impacted trailer #4413259 and the concrete outside the trailer. ERTS will proceed to dispatch a contractor to the site to complete cleanup activities.   Contractors arrived onsite and confirmed approximately 200-gallons of UN2874 Enviroset 40E FNB Resin product released to the entire wooden trailer floor and the concrete beneath the trailer which spread to nine trailer bays, as well as sewer drain was impacted. The contractor applied speedy dry to the release that impacted the concrete and placed booms around the drains as well as the outfall. The estimated 10-gallons still in the tote was solidified with speedy dry and the tote were placed in a roll off for disposal. The contractors flushed the impacted sewer drain and vacuumed and filled (3) totes with impacted water/product. The waste was staged onsite for terminal personnel to manage.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:E-2025030151</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025020053</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025020053&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-13T00:52:39+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-28&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: Plaquemine&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: RI&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: QUALITY CARRIERS INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 1&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: After material was unloaded into consignee&amp;#x27;s storage tank and valves closed, driver was disconnecting hose to tank piping when pressure in hose allowed residue in hose to be released. Small amount of material sprayed onto driver PE and went under gloves onto driver&amp;#x27;s hand. Driver removed gloves and went to Emergency Showers to rinse material from PPE and skin., For driver protection and care he was transported to the hospital ER for evaluation and treatment of skin burn. Driver released from ER and sent home for night. Following day Driver evaluated by personal doctor who recommended he needed surgery to remove some damaged tissue and application of healing skin treatments. Driver admitted to hospital for procedures. Supplemental report will be filed with additional information.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025020053</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report I-2025020006</title>
      <description>
            &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a link="None"&gt;Report I-2025020006&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
            &lt;h4&gt;Identified by scraper @ 2025-03-11T00:50:35+00:00&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;ul&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Incident Date: 2024-12-21&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;City: SOLVAY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;State: NY&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Report Type: A hazardous material incident&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Mode Of Transportation: Highway&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Carrier/Reporter: TERPENING TRUCKING CO., INC.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Hazmat Injuries: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Non-Hazmat Fatalities: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Total Amount Of Damages: 0&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Serious Incident Ind: Yes&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;li&gt;Description: Our driver was transporting a tractor trailer tanker with 11,498 gallons of gasoline heading northbound on Route 60 near the village of Sinclairville, NY. He was traveling at 54 mph when another vehicle traveling southbound turned left in front of our unit. This other vehicle&amp;#x27;s windshield was covered with snow and ice blocking the driver&amp;#x27;s view. This action caused our tractor trailer to rollover striking the guardrail and over turn. The entire unit came to rest upside down against two trees.  Local Sinclairville Fire Emergency response arrived and it was discovered that compartment #1 (3000 gallon capacity) had two puncture wholes mid level and at the top of the tanker. Emergency response used a wax ring to plug the lowest leak point. Compartment #1 retained 486 gallons of gallons of the 3000 loaded. Estimated leak time was under 20 minutes and the leak was halted at that time. The remaining product in 4 compartments retained the original gallons loaded.  Additional resources and Emergency Responders were brought in to assist. Our company transferred to remaining gasoline to another trailer once the trailer was air drilled. New York State DEC was present and monitoring all activities.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
            </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">data-liberation-project:phma-hazmat-incident-reports:I-2025020006</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
